{
  "categories": {
    "Old Testament": {
      "name": "Old Testament",
      "subcategories": {
        "Book summaries": {
          "name": "Book summaries",
          "cards": [
            {
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Genesis",
                "back": "In the Beginning God Created the Heaven and the Earth and Man"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Exodus",
                "back": "From Egypt’s Bondage to Sinai’s Ten Commandments"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Leviticus",
                "back": "Handbook of Worship For Priests"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Numbers",
                "back": "The Wilderness Journey of Israel to Canaan"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Deuteronomy",
                "back": "Repeating the Law for Israel’s Obedience"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Joshua",
                "back": "Promised Land Means Victory"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Judges",
                "back": "The Judges of God’s People"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Ruth",
                "back": "Ruth"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Samuel",
                "back": "Birth of Samuel Through David’s Exile"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 Samuel",
                "back": "History of the Reign of David"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Kings",
                "back": "Solomon Sins, Israel Split"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Chronicles",
                "back": "Death of Saul Through David’s Reign"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 Chronicles",
                "back": "Reign of Solomon Through the Kings of Judah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Ezra",
                "back": "Temple Work"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Nehemiah",
                "back": "Jerusalem Wall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Esther",
                "back": "Purim Feast"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Job",
                "back": "Job God’s Suffering Servant is Tested and Restored"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Psalms",
                "back": "Praise Him"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Proverbs",
                "back": "Understanding and Using God’s Wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Ecclesiastes",
                "back": "Ecclesiastes"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Song of Solomon",
                "back": "The Bride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Isaiah",
                "back": "The Prophecies of Isaiah Concerning the Judgment and Redemption of Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Jeremiah",
                "back": "Prophecies of Jeremiah on the Captivity and Fall of Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Lamentations",
                "back": "Dirge"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Ezekiel",
                "back": "The Prophecies of Ezekiel About Jerusalem and the Temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Daniel",
                "back": "Daniel's Faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Hosea",
                "back": "Gomer the Harlot"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Joel",
                "back": "Cry"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Amos",
                "back": "Judgments"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Obadiah",
                "back": "Esau"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Jonah",
                "back": "Fish"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Micah",
                "back": "Messiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Nahum",
                "back": "God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Habakkuk",
                "back": "Why"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Zephaniah",
                "back": "Jew"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Haggai",
                "back": "Go"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Zechariah",
                "back": "Messiahs Return"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Malachi",
                "back": "Lord"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Matthew",
                "back": "Gospel of Matthew, King of the Jews"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Mark",
                "back": "Christ the Servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Luke",
                "back": "Jesus Christ the Perfect Man"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries John",
                "back": "John the Gospel of Belief"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Acts",
                "back": "Holy Spirit Working in the Church"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Romans",
                "back": "The Gospel of Jesus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Corinthians",
                "back": "Errors in Behavior"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 Corinthians",
                "back": "The True Gospel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Galatians",
                "back": "The Law"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Ephesians",
                "back": "Church"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Philippians",
                "back": "Joys"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Colossians",
                "back": "Hope"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Thessalonians",
                "back": "Faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 Thessalonians",
                "back": "Day"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Timothy",
                "back": "Advice"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 Timothy",
                "back": "Hold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Titus",
                "back": "Son"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Philemon",
                "back": "Love"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Hebrews",
                "back": "New Priesthood"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries James",
                "back": "Works"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 Peter",
                "back": "Trial"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 Peter",
                "back": "Add"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 1 John",
                "back": "Light"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 2 John",
                "back": "Lady"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries 3 John",
                "back": "Gaius"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Jude",
                "back": "Jude"
              },
              {
                "front": "Book summaries Revelation",
                "back": "Prophecy About the Future"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Genesis": {
            "name": "Genesis",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Genesis 1",
                "back": "Inception of the world"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 2",
                "back": "Newlyweds in the garden"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 3",
                "back": "Temptation and man's fall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 4",
                "back": "Hatred and first murder"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 5",
                "back": "Entire genealogy of Adam"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 6",
                "back": "Building of the ark"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 7",
                "back": "Eruption of the flood"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 8",
                "back": "Going from the ark"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 9",
                "back": "Initiation of rainbow covenant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 10",
                "back": "Noah's sons and grandsons"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 11",
                "back": "Nations scattered from Babel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 12",
                "back": "Immigration of Abram's family"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 13",
                "back": "Nephew Lot leaves Abram"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 14",
                "back": "Gifts for Priest Melchizedek"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 15",
                "back": "God counts Abram righteous"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 16",
                "back": "Offspring Ishmael from Hagar"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 17",
                "back": "Designation changed to Abraham"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 18",
                "back": "Compassion for Sodom's righteous"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 19",
                "back": "Ruin of Sodom and Gomorrah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 20",
                "back": "Egypt journey of Abraham"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 21",
                "back": "Arrival of promised Isaac"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 22",
                "back": "Test of Abraham's faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 23",
                "back": "End of Sarah's life"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 24",
                "back": "Discovering Rebekah as bride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 25",
                "back": "Twins Esau, Jacob born"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 26",
                "back": "Hostility between Isaac, Philistines"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 27",
                "back": "Esau robbed of blessing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 28",
                "back": "Heavenly ladder at Bethel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 29",
                "back": "Earning Leah and Rachel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 30",
                "back": "Additions to Jacob's family"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 31",
                "back": "Venture away from Laban"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 32",
                "back": "Endeavoring to wrestle God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 33",
                "back": "New friendship with Esau"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 34",
                "back": "Avenge for Dinah's defilement"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 35",
                "back": "Name changed to Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 36",
                "back": "Descendants of Esau listed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 37",
                "back": "Treachery of Joseph's brothers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 38",
                "back": "Harlot Tamar deceives Judah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 39",
                "back": "Enraged Potiphar jails Joseph"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 40",
                "back": "Explanation of two dreams"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 41",
                "back": "Appointing Joseph as ruler"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 42",
                "back": "Return home without Simeon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 43",
                "back": "Trek to Egypt again"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 44",
                "back": "Holding Benjamin for cup"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 45",
                "back": "Announcement of Joseph's identity"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 46",
                "back": "New home in Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 47",
                "back": "Design to save Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 48",
                "back": "Manasseh and Ephraim adopted"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 49",
                "back": "Announcement of Jacob's blessing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Genesis 50",
                "back": "New relationship among brothers"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Exodus": {
            "name": "Exodus",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Exodus 1",
                "back": "Forced labor for Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 2",
                "back": "Royal training for Moses"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 3",
                "back": "Obstinate Moses resists God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 4",
                "back": "Moses' excuses are answered"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 5",
                "back": "Egyptian oppression is increased"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 6",
                "back": "God's deliverance is promised"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 7",
                "back": "Yahweh smites the Nile"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 8",
                "back": "Plagues of frogs, insects"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 9",
                "back": "Three plagues harden Pharaoh"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 10",
                "back": "Swarming locusts and darkness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 11",
                "back": "Blood required for firstborn"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 12",
                "back": "Observance of the Passover"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 13",
                "back": "National exodus from Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 14",
                "back": "Division of Red Sea"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 15",
                "back": "Adoration song to God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 16",
                "back": "Gathering manna six days"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 17",
                "back": "Extracting water from rock"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 18",
                "back": "Tribal organization for ruling"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 19",
                "back": "Orders at Mount Sinai"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 20",
                "back": "Statement of 10 commandments"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 21",
                "back": "Injunctions for moral justice"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 22",
                "back": "Numerous laws of restitution"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 23",
                "back": "Angelic assistance is promised"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 24",
                "back": "Instructing Moses on Sinai"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 25",
                "back": "Sketch of tabernacle plans"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 26",
                "back": "Tabernacle curtains and boards"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 27",
                "back": "Exact measurements of tabernacle"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 28",
                "back": "Necessary garments for priests"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 29",
                "back": "Consecrations of the priests"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 30",
                "back": "Offerings for sin's atonement"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 31",
                "back": "Mandate to keep Sabbath"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 32",
                "back": "Molten calf brings judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 33",
                "back": "Anguished intercession by Moses"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 34",
                "back": "Renewal of the Covenant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 35",
                "back": "Desire rekindled for tabernacle"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 36",
                "back": "Making curtains and boards"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 37",
                "back": "Explanation of furniture making"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 38",
                "back": "New court for the tabernacle"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 39",
                "back": "Tabernacle and garments finished"
              },
              {
                "front": "Exodus 40",
                "back": "Shekinah glory fills tabernacle"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Leviticus": {
            "name": "Leviticus",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 1",
                "back": "Holiness requires burnt offerings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 2",
                "back": "Acceptance of grain offerings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 3",
                "back": "Necessity of peace offerings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 4",
                "back": "Demand for sin offering"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 5",
                "back": "Burnt offerings for trespasses"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 6",
                "back": "Offering laws for priests"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 7",
                "back": "Offering laws for priests"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 8",
                "back": "Keeping the priest consecrated"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 9",
                "back": "Offering of Aaron's sacrifice"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 10",
                "back": "Fire consumes Nadab, Abihu"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 11",
                "back": "Warning against unclean animals"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 12",
                "back": "Offerings for birth purification"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 13",
                "back": "Requirements for unclean lepers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 14",
                "back": "Sign of cleansing leapers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 15",
                "back": "Hygiene for human uncleanness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 16",
                "back": "Instituting Day of Atonement"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 17",
                "back": "Prominence of the blood"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 18",
                "back": "Forbidding of sexual impurities"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 19",
                "back": "Orders to be holy"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 20",
                "back": "Restrictions against moral sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 21",
                "back": "Priests qualifications before God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 22",
                "back": "Respect for God's offerings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 23",
                "back": "Institution of religious feasts"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 24",
                "back": "Eating the holy bread"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 25",
                "back": "Sabbatical year and jubilee"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 26",
                "back": "Trouble promised for disobedience"
              },
              {
                "front": "Leviticus 27",
                "back": "Seriousness of keeping vows"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Numbers": {
            "name": "Numbers",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Numbers 1",
                "back": "Tallying Israel by tribes"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 2",
                "back": "Host organized for marching"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 3",
                "back": "Exchanging Levites for firstborn"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 4",
                "back": "Work of the Levites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 5",
                "back": "Instructions for jealousy laws"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 6",
                "back": "Law of Nazirite, Aaronic blessing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 7",
                "back": "Dedication of leaders' offerings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 8",
                "back": "Emphasis on Levitical cleansing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 9",
                "back": "Record of second Passover"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 10",
                "back": "Nation leaves Mount Sinai"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 11",
                "back": "Elders and quails given"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 12",
                "back": "Sin of Miriam's murmuring"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 13",
                "back": "Spies sent from Kadeshbarnea"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 14",
                "back": "Judgment on Israel's unbelief"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 15",
                "back": "Offerings for the land"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 16",
                "back": "Uprising led by Korah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 17",
                "back": "Rod of Aaron buds"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 18",
                "back": "Necessity of priestly service"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 19",
                "back": "Eleazar and red heifer"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 20",
                "back": "Years of wandering end"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 21",
                "back": "Overthrow of the Amorites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 22",
                "back": "Fear of Balaam's donkey"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 23",
                "back": "Inspiration of Balaam's prophecies"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 24",
                "back": "Series of Balaam's prophecies"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 25",
                "back": "Reward of Phineas' zeal"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 26",
                "back": "Audit of Israel's tribes"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 27",
                "back": "Endorsement of Joshua's leading"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 28",
                "back": "Law of offerings reviewed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 29",
                "back": "Teachings for seventh month"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 30",
                "back": "Oath and vow laws"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 31",
                "back": "Conquest of the Midianites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 32",
                "back": "Abode of Reuben, Gad"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 33",
                "back": "Naming of Israel's journeys"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 34",
                "back": "Assigning borders of lands"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 35",
                "back": "Appointing cities of refuge"
              },
              {
                "front": "Numbers 36",
                "back": "Necessity of tribal marriage"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Deuteronomy": {
            "name": "Deuteronomy",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 1",
                "back": "Retelling of Israel's failures"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 2",
                "back": "End of wilderness years"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 3",
                "back": "Possessing Gilead and Bashan"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 4",
                "back": "Exhortation to obey God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 5",
                "back": "Assessing the 10 Commandments"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 6",
                "back": "Teaching children the law"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 7",
                "back": "Idolatry warned; obedience blessed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 8",
                "back": "Necessity of God's testing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 9",
                "back": "God's grace after intercession"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 10",
                "back": "Tablets for the ark"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 11",
                "back": "Heritage for obeying God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 12",
                "back": "Enjoy the holy separation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 13",
                "back": "Lying enticers are stoned"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 14",
                "back": "Animals suitable for eating"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 15",
                "back": "Way of releasing debts"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 16",
                "back": "Feasts listed and explained"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 17",
                "back": "Obliteration of all evildoers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 18",
                "back": "Rights of Levites, future Prophet"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 19",
                "back": "Involuntary killer given refuge"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 20",
                "back": "Strategy for God's warfare"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 21",
                "back": "Rebellious son is punished"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 22",
                "back": "Adultery and morality laws"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 23",
                "back": "Exclusions from the assemblies"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 24",
                "back": "Leaving a mate legally"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 25",
                "back": "Summary of civil laws"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 26",
                "back": "Offering of firstfruits"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 27",
                "back": "Building the Ebal altar"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 28",
                "back": "Extended blessings and cursings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 29",
                "back": "Disobedience will bring curses"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 30",
                "back": "Initiative for following God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 31",
                "back": "Establishment of Joshua's leading"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 32",
                "back": "New song of Moses"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 33",
                "back": "Conferring the tribal blessings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Deuteronomy 34",
                "back": "End of Moses' life"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Joshua": {
            "name": "Joshua",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Joshua 1",
                "back": "Prosperity promised for obedience"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 2",
                "back": "Rahab protects two spies"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 3",
                "back": "Onward through the Jordan"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 4",
                "back": "Memorial stones are set"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 5",
                "back": "Israel's circumcision at Gilgal"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 6",
                "back": "Successful conquest of Jericho"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 7",
                "back": "End of Achan's coveting"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 8",
                "back": "Defeat of Ai's army"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 9",
                "back": "Lying by the Gibeonites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 10",
                "back": "Attack of five kings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 11",
                "back": "Northern kings are conquered"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 12",
                "back": "Diary of defeated kings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 13",
                "back": "Moses' division, remaining land"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 14",
                "back": "Expectations of Caleb rewarded"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 15",
                "back": "Apportionment to Judah's sons"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 16",
                "back": "Niche for Ephraim tribe"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 17",
                "back": "Selfishness of Manasseh satisfied"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 18",
                "back": "Victory proclaimed in Shiloh"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 19",
                "back": "Inheritance to six sons"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 20",
                "back": "Cities of refuge named"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 21",
                "back": "Towns of Levites named"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 22",
                "back": "Offence of the altar"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 23",
                "back": "Rehearsing of the law"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joshua 24",
                "back": "Years of Joshua ended"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Judges": {
            "name": "Judges",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Judges 1",
                "back": "Territories Israel left unconquered"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 2",
                "back": "How God tested Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 3",
                "back": "Ehud/Moab, Othniel/Cushan"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 4",
                "back": "Jabin overcome by Deborah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 5",
                "back": "Uplifting song of Deborah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 6",
                "back": "Determination via Gideon's fleece"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 7",
                "back": "Gideon's army routs Midianites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 8",
                "back": "Ephod causes Gideon's downfall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 9",
                "back": "Shechemites make Abimilech king"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 10",
                "back": "Oppression by the Ammonites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 11",
                "back": "Fighting Jephthah subdues Ammonites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 12",
                "back": "Gileadites overcome Ephraimites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 13",
                "back": "Offspring Samson to Manoah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 14",
                "back": "Deceit over Samson's riddle"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 15",
                "back": "Samson kills thousand Philistines"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 16",
                "back": "Prying Delilah gets Samson's secret"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 17",
                "back": "Ephraimite Micah hires priest"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 18",
                "back": "Offenses committed by Danites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 19",
                "back": "Perversion of Levite's concubine"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 20",
                "back": "Levite's vengeance on Benjamites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Judges 21",
                "back": "Existence of Benjamin assured"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Ruth": {
            "name": "Ruth",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Ruth 1",
                "back": "Ruth returns with Naomi"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ruth 2",
                "back": "Unlimited gleaning from Boaz"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ruth 3",
                "back": "Trying for kinsman redeemer"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ruth 4",
                "back": "Husband Boaz to David"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Samuel": {
            "name": "1 Samuel",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 1",
                "back": "Birth of Hannah’s son"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 2",
                "back": "Immorality of Eli’s sons"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 3",
                "back": "Revelation of Eli’s judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 4",
                "back": "Tragedy of ark’s capture"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 5",
                "back": "Heavenly glory leaves Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 6",
                "back": "Offerings with returned ark"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 7",
                "back": "Foreign gods are removed"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 8",
                "back": "Stubborn request for king"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 9",
                "back": "Appointment of Saul arranged"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 10",
                "back": "Making Saul Israel’s king"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 11",
                "back": "Unified defense of Jabesh"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 12",
                "back": "Exhortation against demanding king"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 13",
                "back": "Lesson of Saul’s foolishness"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 14",
                "back": "Triumph of Jonathan’s attack"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 15",
                "back": "Hopelessness of Saul’s disobedience"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 16",
                "back": "Record of David’s anointing"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 17",
                "back": "Outdoing Goliath of Gath"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 18",
                "back": "Unfriendly Saul threatens David"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 19",
                "back": "Guarding David from Saul"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 20",
                "back": "Helpful Jonathan shields David"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 21",
                "back": "David demands priest’s provisions"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 22",
                "back": "Ahimilech killed by Saul"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 23",
                "back": "Victory over the Philistines"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 24",
                "back": "Integrity shown by David"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 25",
                "back": "Death of Samuel mourned"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 26",
                "back": "Saul spared second time"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 27",
                "back": "Exile in Philistine territory"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 28",
                "back": "X-tended séance with witch"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 29",
                "back": "Intentions of David questioned"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 30",
                "back": "Loss of Ziklag avenged"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Samuel 31",
                "back": "End of Saul’s life"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Samuel": {
            "name": "2 Samuel",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 1",
                "back": "Heaviness of David’s heart"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 2",
                "back": "Ishbosheth made Israel’s king"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 3",
                "back": "Sadness over Abner’s death"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 4",
                "back": "Torture of Ishbosheth’s killers"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 5",
                "back": "Outset of David’s reign"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 6",
                "back": "Relocating ark to Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 7",
                "back": "Yearning to build temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 8",
                "back": "Opponents defeated by David"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 9",
                "back": "Favor shown to Mephibosheth"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 10",
                "back": "Triumph over Ammonite alliance"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 11",
                "back": "Hypocrisy of David’s adultery"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 12",
                "back": "Effects of David’s sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 13",
                "back": "Rape of Tamar by Amnon"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 14",
                "back": "Exiled Absalom comes home"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 15",
                "back": "Insurrection led by Absalom"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 16",
                "back": "Gravity of Ahithophel’s advice"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 17",
                "back": "Nature of Hushai’s counsel"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 18",
                "back": "Opposition by Absalom ends"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 19",
                "back": "Forgiving of Absalom’s followers"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 20",
                "back": "Death of rebellious Sheba"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 21",
                "back": "Averting wrath of famine"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 22",
                "back": "Victory psalm by David"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 23",
                "back": "Identity of mighty men"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Samuel 24",
                "back": "David’s census brings plague"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Kings": {
            "name": "1 Kings",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 1",
                "back": "Solomon anointed Israel’s king"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 2",
                "back": "Opponents of David killed"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 3",
                "back": "Lord gives Solomon wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 4",
                "back": "Officers of King Solomon"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 5",
                "back": "Materials for temple requested"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 6",
                "back": "Overall temple is completed"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 7",
                "back": "Nature of Hiram's work"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 8",
                "back": "Solomon's prayer of dedication"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 9",
                "back": "Instruction for Solomon's covenant"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 10",
                "back": "Numerous riches and wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 11",
                "back": "Solomon's wives bring idolatry"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 12",
                "back": "Insurrection of northern tribes"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 13",
                "back": "Sin of unnamed prophet"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 14",
                "back": "Reign of Jeroboam (N) Rehoboam (S)"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 15",
                "back": "Abijam (S), Asa+(S), Nadab (N) Baasha (N)"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 16",
                "back": "Elah (N), Zimri (N), Omri/Tibni (N), Ahab (N)"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 17",
                "back": "Lord provides Elijah's food"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 18",
                "back": "Sovereignty shown on Carmel"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 19",
                "back": "Prophet Elijah calls Elisha"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 20",
                "back": "Loss by Syrian army"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 21",
                "back": "Injustice in Naboth's vineyard"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Kings 22",
                "back": "Termination of Ahab, Jehoshaphat+(S), Ahaziah (N)"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Chronicles": {
            "name": "1 Chronicles",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 1",
                "back": "Descendants Adam to Edom"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 2",
                "back": "Each descendant of Judah"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 3",
                "back": "All of David’s sons"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 4",
                "back": "Tribes of Judah, Simeon"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 5",
                "back": "Houses of Rueben, Gad"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 6",
                "back": "Offspring of Levi’s sons"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 7",
                "back": "Families of Issachar, Naphtali, Manasseh, Ephraim, Asher"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 8",
                "back": "Sons of Benjamin’s tribe"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 9",
                "back": "Assigned positions for Levites"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 10",
                "back": "Ugly end of Saul"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 11",
                "back": "Leaders in David’s army"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 12",
                "back": "Tribal totals of army"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 13",
                "back": "Hand on ark disciplined"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 14",
                "back": "Raids of Philistines repelled"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 15",
                "back": "Obtaining ark for Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 16",
                "back": "United celebration at tabernacle"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 17",
                "back": "God’s covenant with David"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 18",
                "back": "Harmony through David’s reign"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 19",
                "back": "Defeat of Ammon, Syria"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 20",
                "back": "Assault against Rabbah, Philistines"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 21",
                "back": "Verdict against David’s census"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 22",
                "back": "Instructions to build temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 23",
                "back": "David organizes Levitical duties"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 24",
                "back": "Schedule of priests’ service"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 25",
                "back": "Responsibilities of temple musicians"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 26",
                "back": "Employment for gate keepers"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 27",
                "back": "Israelite army division commanders"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 28",
                "back": "Guidelines for building temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Chronicles 29",
                "back": "Necessary materials given gladly"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Chronicles": {
            "name": "2 Chronicles",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 1",
                "back": "Request for God’s wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 2",
                "back": "Enlistment of Hiram’s help"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 3",
                "back": "Initiation of temple construction"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 4",
                "back": "Garnishments of the temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 5",
                "back": "New home for ark"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 6",
                "back": "Offering temple dedication prayer"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 7",
                "back": "Filling temple with glory"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 8",
                "back": "Solomon’s cities and sacrifices"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 9",
                "back": "Observations by Sheba’s queen"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 10",
                "back": "Leaders reject Rehoboam’s harshness"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 11",
                "back": "Offenses strengthened by Rehoboam"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 12",
                "back": "Mistake of Rehoboam judged"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 13",
                "back": "Overcoming Israel under Abijah"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 14",
                "back": "Narrative of Asa’s faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 15",
                "back": "Temporal reforms of Asa"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 16",
                "back": "Hypocrisy and Asa’s death"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 17",
                "back": "Revival under king Jehoshaphat"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 18",
                "back": "Offensive prophesy by Micaiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 19",
                "back": "Use of impartial judges"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 20",
                "back": "God’s victory over Moab"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 21",
                "back": "Horrible reign of Jehoram"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 22",
                "back": "Terrible reign of Ahaziah"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 23",
                "back": "Hailing Joash+ as king"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 24",
                "back": "Expenses of temple repairs"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 25",
                "back": "Keeping idols defeats Amaziah"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 26",
                "back": "Incenses offered by Uzziah"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 27",
                "back": "Normal reign of Jotham+ 28GrosssinsofAhaz"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 29",
                "back": "Spiritual reign of Hezekiah+"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 30",
                "back": "Observance of the Passover"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 31",
                "back": "Further reforms of Hezekiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 32",
                "back": "Judah invaded by Assyria"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 33",
                "back": "Unfortunate reign of Manasseh, Amon"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 34",
                "back": "Discovery of the law (Josiah+)"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 35",
                "back": "Account of Passover observance"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Chronicles 36",
                "back": "Horrible captivity under Jehoichin"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Ezra": {
            "name": "Ezra",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Ezra 1",
                "back": "Temple proclamation by Cyrus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 2",
                "back": "Exiles return under Zerubbabel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 3",
                "back": "Making the temple foundation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 4",
                "back": "Postponement of the work"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 5",
                "back": "Letter written to Darius"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 6",
                "back": "Exiles finish the temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 7",
                "back": "Warrant authorizing Ezra’s return"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 8",
                "back": "Outline of Ezra’s return"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 9",
                "back": "Repentance prayer by Ezra"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezra 10",
                "back": "Keeping from pagan wives"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Nehemiah": {
            "name": "Nehemiah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 1",
                "back": "Jerusalem’s tragic plight mourned"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 2",
                "back": "Enlisting the king’s support"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 3",
                "back": "Record of all workers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 4",
                "back": "Undermining attacks by Samaritans"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 5",
                "back": "Selling Jewish children renounced"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 6",
                "back": "Assembling wall despite opposition"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 7",
                "back": "Ledger of returning Jews"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 8",
                "back": "Explanation of God’s law"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 9",
                "back": "Making confessions of sins"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 10",
                "back": "Witnesses to signed covenant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 11",
                "back": "Account of Jerusalem dwellers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 12",
                "back": "Levites return to temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nehemiah 13",
                "back": "Levying reforms of Nehemiah"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Esther": {
            "name": "Esther",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Esther 1",
                "back": "Persian decree against Vashti"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 2",
                "back": "Uncle Mordecai saves king"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 3",
                "back": "Revenge plotted by Haman"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 4",
                "back": "Intersession made to Esther"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 5",
                "back": "Making dinner for king"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 6",
                "back": "Favor shown to Mordecai"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 7",
                "back": "Esther requests her life"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 8",
                "back": "Ahasuerus gives second decree"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 9",
                "back": "Sons of Haman hanged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Esther 10",
                "back": "Testimony to Mordecai’s greatness"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Job": {
            "name": "Job",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Job 1",
                "back": "Job’s prosperity and tragedies"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 2",
                "back": "Outbreak against Job physically"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 3",
                "back": "Birth cursed by Job"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 4",
                "back": "Gather what is sown (Ez)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 5",
                "back": "Ordinary case of chastening (Ez)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 6",
                "back": "Denial of Eliphaz’s charge (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 7",
                "back": "Supplication against God’s testing (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 8",
                "back": "Suffering befalls only wicked (Bu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 9",
                "back": "Unfortunate helplessness of man (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 10",
                "back": "Fairness of God questioned (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 11",
                "back": "Finite man must repent (Z)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 12",
                "back": "Evident truths animals know (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 13",
                "back": "Resolution to debate God (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 14",
                "back": "Insignificance of man’s destiny (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 15",
                "back": "Necessity of sin’s punishment (Ez)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 16",
                "back": "God’s affliction for innocence (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 17",
                "back": "Salvation only in death (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 18",
                "back": "End of wicked described (B)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 19",
                "back": "Redeemer is hoped for (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 20",
                "back": "Vengeance on wicked certain (Z)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 21",
                "back": "Antithesis of rich wicked (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 22",
                "back": "Neglect of good deeds (Ez)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 23",
                "back": "Tired of seeking God (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 24",
                "back": "Inquisition on unpunished sin (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 25",
                "back": "Submission of unjust men (B)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 26",
                "back": "Transcendence of God’s greatness (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 27",
                "back": "Evildoers’ fate in life (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 28",
                "back": "Source of man’s wisdom (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 29",
                "back": "Triumphs of Job’s past (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 30",
                "back": "Expression of Job’s plight (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 31",
                "back": "Denial of false charges (J)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 32",
                "back": "Analysis by young Elihu (Eu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 33",
                "back": "Nature of God’s revelation (Eu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 34",
                "back": "Discipline reason for trials (Eu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 35",
                "back": "Repudiation of Job’s protests (Eu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 36",
                "back": "Explanation of God’s ways (Eu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 37",
                "back": "Sovereignty of God’s ways (Eu)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 38",
                "back": "Tough questions are answered (G)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 39",
                "back": "Ordinary animals show ignorance (G)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 40",
                "back": "Revelation of Job’s impotence (G)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 41",
                "back": "Example of leviathan’s power (G)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Job 42",
                "back": "Deliverance from Job’s trials"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Psalms": {
            "name": "Psalms",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Psalms Praise psalms",
                "back": "9, 18, 21, 30, 47, 48, 63, 67, 71, 75, 84, 89, 92, 96, 99, 100, 103, 108, 111, 112, 113, 115-117, 124, 134, 135, 138, 145-150"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Remorse psalms",
                "back": "32, 38, 39, 51, 79, 85, 101, 130, 143"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Acrostic psalms",
                "back": 119
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Imprecatory psalms",
                "back": "10, 35, 52, 55, 56, 58, 59, 64, 69, 83, 109, 125, 129, 137, 140, 141, 144"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Supplication psalms",
                "back": "3, 4, 6, 11-13, 20,25-28, 36, 42, 43, 54, 57, 60, 61, 70, 74, 80, 86, 88, 90, 120, 122, 123, 142"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Environmental psalms",
                "back": "8, 19, 29, 33, 65, 93, 98, 104"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Historical psalms",
                "back": "44, 66, 77, 78, 81, 95, 105, 106, 114, 132, 136"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Instructional psalms",
                "back": "1, 5, 7, 14, 15, 17, 34, 37, 49, 50, 53, 62, 73, 76, 82, 87, 91, 94, 107, 121, 126-128, 131, 133, 139"
              },
              {
                "front": "Psalms Messianic psalms",
                "back": "2, 16, 22-24, 31, 40, 41, 45, 46, 68, 72, 97, 102, 110, 118"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Proverbs": {
            "name": "Proverbs",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 1",
                "back": "Usefulness of God’s wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 2",
                "back": "Nature of strange women"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 3",
                "back": "Discipline results in wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 4",
                "back": "Exhortation to get wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 5",
                "back": "Results of sinful lust"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 6",
                "back": "Sluggard, ant, strange women"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 7",
                "back": "Temptation by strange women"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 8",
                "back": "Appeal to God’s wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 9",
                "back": "Necessity for the righteous"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 10",
                "back": "Diligence compared to slothfulness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 11",
                "back": "Instructions for the righteous"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 12",
                "back": "Nature of the righteous"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 13",
                "back": "Good understanding produces favor"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 14",
                "back": "Applications for the wise"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 15",
                "back": "New use of tongue"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 16",
                "back": "Destruction of the proud"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 17",
                "back": "Unity of good friends"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 18",
                "back": "Safety through God’s wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 19",
                "back": "Instruction on personal priorities"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 20",
                "back": "Nobility of trusting God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 21",
                "back": "Governor of men’s hearts"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 22",
                "back": "Good reputation in life"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 23",
                "back": "Offenses of loving riches"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 24",
                "back": "Description of evil men"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 25",
                "back": "Solomon’s proverbs on humility"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 26",
                "back": "Ways of the fool"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 27",
                "back": "Illusion of man’s wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 28",
                "back": "Senselessness of denying sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 29",
                "back": "Delights of godly wisdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 30",
                "back": "Oracles given by Agur"
              },
              {
                "front": "Proverbs 31",
                "back": "Marks of virtuous woman"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Ecclesiastes": {
            "name": "Ecclesiastes",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 1",
                "back": "Emptiness of accumulating wealth"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 2",
                "back": "Conclusion to seeking pleasure"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 3",
                "back": "Completeness of God’s timing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 4",
                "back": "Labor is also vanity"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 5",
                "back": "End of gain and honor"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 6",
                "back": "Sin is never satisfying"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 7",
                "back": "Inadequacy of being affluent"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 8",
                "back": "Abuse of God’s authority"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 9",
                "back": "Same end for all"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 10",
                "back": "Temporary wisdom of man"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 11",
                "back": "Emptiness of godless living"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ecclesiastes 12",
                "back": "Serving God brings satisfaction"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Song of Solomon": {
            "name": "Song of Solomon",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 1",
                "back": "Testimony of bride’s love"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 2",
                "back": "Heart yearnings of bride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 3",
                "back": "Expectations of the bride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 4",
                "back": "Bridegroom expresses his love"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 5",
                "back": "Response of the bride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 6",
                "back": "Interval when two separated"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 7",
                "back": "Desire expressed for intimacy"
              },
              {
                "front": "Song of Solomon 8",
                "back": "Expectations of the bride"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Isaiah": {
            "name": "Isaiah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 1",
                "back": "Truth of Israel’s corruption"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 2",
                "back": "Hopelessness of Israel’s pride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 3",
                "back": "Execution of Judah’s leaders"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 4",
                "back": "Purging sin from Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 5",
                "back": "Removal of God’s vineyard"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 6",
                "back": "Opening of Isaiah’s lips"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 7",
                "back": "Prophecy of virgin’s child"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 8",
                "back": "Horror of Assyrian invasion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 9",
                "back": "Establishing of Messiah’s kingdom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 10",
                "back": "Callousness of Assyrian army"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 11",
                "back": "Intervention of Jesse’s branch"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 12",
                "back": "Exalting the Lord’s salvation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 13",
                "back": "Sure destruction of Babylon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 14",
                "back": "Overthrow of proud Lucifer"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 15",
                "back": "Failure of Moab predicted"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 16",
                "back": "Invasion of Moab’s fall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 17",
                "back": "Sins of Damascus exposed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 18",
                "back": "Announcement of Ethiopia’s doom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 19",
                "back": "Iniquities of Egypt judged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 20",
                "back": "Assyria takes Egyptians captive"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 21",
                "back": "Horrible vision of Babylon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 22",
                "back": "Calamity in Jerusalem foretold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 23",
                "back": "Oracle given concerning Tyre"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 24",
                "back": "Nations judged by God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 25",
                "back": "Cries of praise God-ward"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 26",
                "back": "Exaltation of restored Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 27",
                "back": "Restoration of God’s people"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 28",
                "back": "Northern Kingdom is warned"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 29",
                "back": "Impending discipline of Ariel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 30",
                "back": "No help from Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 31",
                "back": "God’s judgment of Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 32",
                "back": "Triumph of righteous king"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 33",
                "back": "Hopeless future of Assyria"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 34",
                "back": "End of Edom predicted"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 35",
                "back": "Joyful shouting in Zion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 36",
                "back": "Upsetting news for Hezekiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 37",
                "back": "Doom comes to Sennacherib"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 38",
                "back": "God grants Hezekiah's prayer"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 39",
                "back": "Messengers arrive from Babylon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 40",
                "back": "Eternal comfort from God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 41",
                "back": "Nature of God's power"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 42",
                "back": "Triumph of God's servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 43",
                "back": "Assurance of Israel's forgiveness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 44",
                "back": "Nonsense of serving idols"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 45",
                "back": "Deliverance by king Cyrus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 46",
                "back": "Ruin of Babylon's idols"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 47",
                "back": "End of Babylon's existence"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 48",
                "back": "Deliverance of Israel promised"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 49",
                "back": "Expectation of God's Servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 50",
                "back": "Mercy through God’s Servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 51",
                "back": "Patience of God's salvation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 52",
                "back": "Torture of God's Servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 53",
                "back": "Intercession of God's Servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 54",
                "back": "Offer of God's compassion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 55",
                "back": "Necessity of seeking God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 56",
                "back": "Obedience required by God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 57",
                "back": "False leaders are rebuked"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 58",
                "back": "Jehovah's requirements for holiness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 59",
                "back": "Evil blocks God's blessing"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 60",
                "back": "Risen glory of Zion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 61",
                "back": "Unveiling of Messiah's work"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 62",
                "back": "Salvation promised to Zion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 63",
                "back": "Ancient mercies are recalled"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 64",
                "back": "Lord's remnant gives thanks"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 65",
                "back": "Eternal heaven and earth"
              },
              {
                "front": "Isaiah 66",
                "back": "Message of Zion's future"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Jeremiah": {
            "name": "Jeremiah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 1",
                "back": "Prophet Jeremiah is called"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 2",
                "back": "Review of Jerusalem's apostasy"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 3",
                "back": "Offer of God's pardon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 4",
                "back": "Prediction of Judah's ruin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 5",
                "back": "Horror of Judah's punishment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 6",
                "back": "Enemy conquers form north"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 7",
                "back": "Counterfeit worship of God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 8",
                "back": "Insensitivity toward Judah's sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 9",
                "back": "Exile and ruin foretold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 10",
                "back": "Senselessness of idol worship"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 11",
                "back": "Outcome of Judah's disobedience"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 12",
                "back": "Faithfulness of God's judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 13",
                "back": "Jeremiah hides linen girdle"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 14",
                "back": "Exhortation about coming drought"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 15",
                "back": "Repentance no longer option"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 16",
                "back": "Exile and return predicted"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 17",
                "back": "Misdirection of man's heart"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 18",
                "back": "Illustration from potter's house"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 19",
                "back": "Annihilation of potter's vessel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 20",
                "back": "Hopelessness felt by Jeremiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 21",
                "back": "Overthrow of Jerusalem imminent"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 22",
                "back": "Nation of Judah warned"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 23",
                "back": "True and false shepherds"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 24",
                "back": "Hearts return to God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 25",
                "back": "Elimination of lying prophets"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 26",
                "back": "Conspiracy to murder Jeremiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 27",
                "back": "Allegiance to king encouraged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 28",
                "back": "Prophet Hananiah is judged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 29",
                "back": "Time of Israel's restoration"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 30",
                "back": "Israel's deliverance is promised"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 31",
                "back": "Voicing the new covenant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 32",
                "back": "Inside prison Jeremiah prays"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 33",
                "back": "Throne of David's branch"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 34",
                "back": "Years of Zedekiah reviewed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 35",
                "back": "Acceptance of the Rechabites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 36",
                "back": "New scroll is written"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 37",
                "back": "Detention in the prison"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 38",
                "back": "Final chance for Zedekiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 39",
                "back": "Announcement of Jerusalem's fall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 40",
                "back": "Loyal Jeremiah remains behind"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 41",
                "back": "Lowly crimes of Ishmael"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 42",
                "back": "Offense of trusting Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 43",
                "back": "Flight to Egypt wrong"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 44",
                "back": "Jews threatened in Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 45",
                "back": "Error of Baruch's selfishness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 46",
                "back": "Ruin of Egypt foretold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 47",
                "back": "Upset of Philistines foretold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 48",
                "back": "Siege of Moab predicted"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 49",
                "back": "Attacks on surrounding nations"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 50",
                "back": "Lofty Babylon will fall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 51",
                "back": "Extinction of Babylon foretold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jeremiah 52",
                "back": "Memorial of Jerusalem's fall"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Lamentations": {
            "name": "Lamentations",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Lamentations 1",
                "back": "Desolation of Jerusalem announced"
              },
              {
                "front": "Lamentations 2",
                "back": "Israel's misery is lamented"
              },
              {
                "front": "Lamentations 3",
                "back": "Reminder of God's mercy"
              },
              {
                "front": "Lamentations 4",
                "back": "Grimness of Israel's sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Lamentations 5",
                "back": "Exiles pray for mercy"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Ezekiel": {
            "name": "Ezekiel",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 1",
                "back": "Throne vision of Ezekiel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 2",
                "back": "Hearing of God's call"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 3",
                "back": "Endowment of God's Spirit"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 4",
                "back": "Portrayal of Jerusalem's judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 5",
                "back": "Razor pictures Israel's punishment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 6",
                "back": "Obliteration of high places"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 7",
                "back": "Powerless Israel against God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 8",
                "back": "Horrible sins in temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 9",
                "back": "Execution of Jerusalem's idolaters"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 10",
                "back": "Cherubim seen leaving temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 11",
                "back": "Idolatrous leaders are judged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 12",
                "back": "Exile dramatized by Ezekiel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 13",
                "back": "Statement against false prophets"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 14",
                "back": "Order to forsake idols"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 15",
                "back": "Fire to consume Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 16",
                "back": "Examples of spiritual prostitution"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 17",
                "back": "Zedekiah rebels against Babylon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 18",
                "back": "Each person held responsible"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 19",
                "back": "King like trapped animal"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 20",
                "back": "Israel's history of rebellion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 21",
                "back": "Executioner's sword over Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 22",
                "back": "Legal case against Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 23",
                "back": "Assyrians and Babylonians coming"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 24",
                "back": "Boiling pot pictures judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 25",
                "back": "Other surrounding nations judged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 26",
                "back": "Utter destruction of Tyre"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 27",
                "back": "Tyre lamented for desolation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 28",
                "back": "Judgment of king's pride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 29",
                "back": "Egypt will become desolate"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 30",
                "back": "Ruthless Babylon destroys Egypt"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 31",
                "back": "Undoing of Pharaoh's pride"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 32",
                "back": "Slaying of Pharaoh's army"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 33",
                "back": "Announcement of Jerusalem's fall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 34",
                "back": "Love of great shepherd"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 35",
                "back": "Exaltation over Edom's desolation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 36",
                "back": "Miraculous restoration of Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 37",
                "back": "Announcement of Israel's regathering"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 38",
                "back": "Nations allied with Gog"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 39",
                "back": "Destruction of Gog predicted"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 40",
                "back": "Temple courtyard is measured"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 41",
                "back": "Holy place is measured"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 42",
                "back": "Every chamber is measured"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 43",
                "back": "Temple filled with glory"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 44",
                "back": "Excluding some from temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 45",
                "back": "Mandates regarding the prince"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 46",
                "back": "Prince's passageways and offerings"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 47",
                "back": "Land boundaries of Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ezekiel 48",
                "back": "Each tribe given territory"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Daniel": {
            "name": "Daniel",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Daniel 1",
                "back": "Daniel favored by Nebuchadnezzar"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 2",
                "back": "Answer to king's dream"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 3",
                "back": "Nebuchadnezzar's furnace of fire"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 4",
                "back": "Interpretation of tree vision"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 5",
                "back": "Events at Belshazzar's feast"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 6",
                "back": "Lion's den of Darius"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 7",
                "back": "Scenes of coming kingdoms"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 8",
                "back": "Features of four beasts"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 9",
                "back": "Appointing the seventy weeks"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 10",
                "back": "Interpreting the final vision"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 11",
                "back": "Terror of the king"
              },
              {
                "front": "Daniel 12",
                "back": "Hope of end times"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Hosea": {
            "name": "Hosea",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Hosea 1",
                "back": "Gomer's marriage and children"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 2",
                "back": "Offenses of Gomer condemned"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 3",
                "back": "Message of second marriage"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 4",
                "back": "Error of Israel's ways"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 5",
                "back": "Rebuke of Israel's leaders"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 6",
                "back": "Testimony of God's love"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 7",
                "back": "Hopelessness of Israel's desertion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 8",
                "back": "Exile unavoidable for Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 9",
                "back": "Harlotry will be punished"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 10",
                "back": "Assyria will enslave Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 11",
                "back": "Rebellion against God's love"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 12",
                "back": "Legal case against Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 13",
                "back": "Overthrow of Ephraim certain"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hosea 14",
                "back": "Transformation if Israel repents"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Joel": {
            "name": "Joel",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Joel 1",
                "back": "Cry to avoid judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joel 2",
                "back": "Repent on Day of the Lord"
              },
              {
                "front": "Joel 3",
                "back": "Yahweh judges the nations"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Amos": {
            "name": "Amos",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Amos 1",
                "back": "Judgment of the nations"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 2",
                "back": "Ungodliness of Israel explained"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 3",
                "back": "Destruction of Israel coming"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 4",
                "back": "God's reproofs went unnoticed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 5",
                "back": "Making plea for repentance"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 6",
                "back": "Elimination of unrighteous wealthy"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 7",
                "back": "Nature of God's judgments"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 8",
                "back": "Time ripe for judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Amos 9",
                "back": "Scattering and Israel's restoration"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Obadiah": {
            "name": "Obadiah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Obadiah 43474",
                "back": "Edom's doom is prophesied"
              },
              {
                "front": "Obadiah 43752",
                "back": "Sins of the Edomites"
              },
              {
                "front": "Obadiah 15-16",
                "back": "Accountability of all nations"
              },
              {
                "front": "Obadiah 17-21",
                "back": "Ultimate restoration of Israel"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Jonah": {
            "name": "Jonah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Jonah 1",
                "back": "Flight from God's presence"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jonah 2",
                "back": "Intercession from within fish"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jonah 3",
                "back": "Sackcloth worn in Nineveh"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jonah 4",
                "back": "Human failure of Jonah"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Micah": {
            "name": "Micah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Micah 1",
                "back": "Messages against Samaria, Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Micah 2",
                "back": "Evils of Israel's people"
              },
              {
                "front": "Micah 3",
                "back": "Sins of Israel's leaders"
              },
              {
                "front": "Micah 4",
                "back": "Sovereign king in Zion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Micah 5",
                "back": "Introduction of Bethlehem's Messiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Micah 6",
                "back": "Actions of injustice rebuked"
              },
              {
                "front": "Micah 7",
                "back": "Hope in God's future"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Nahum": {
            "name": "Nahum",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Nahum 1",
                "back": "God's character and judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nahum 2",
                "back": "Overthrow of Nineveh imminent"
              },
              {
                "front": "Nahum 3",
                "back": "Details of Nineveh's judgment"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Habakkuk": {
            "name": "Habakkuk",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Habakkuk 1",
                "back": "Why is evil unpunished"
              },
              {
                "front": "Habakkuk 2",
                "back": "Haughty Chaldea will fall"
              },
              {
                "front": "Habakkuk 3",
                "back": "Yielding to God's sovereignty"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Zephaniah": {
            "name": "Zephaniah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Zephaniah 1",
                "back": "Judah's day of wrath"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zephaniah 2",
                "back": "Enemies of Judah punished"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zephaniah 3",
                "back": "Wrath and coming restoration"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Haggai": {
            "name": "Haggai",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Haggai 1",
                "back": "God's temple needs building"
              },
              {
                "front": "Haggai 2",
                "back": "Older temple less glorious"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Zechariah": {
            "name": "Zechariah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 1",
                "back": "Meaning of Zechariah's vision"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 2",
                "back": "Examination with measuring line"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 3",
                "back": "Satan and the branch"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 4",
                "back": "Seven lampstands of gold"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 5",
                "back": "Interpreting the flying scroll"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 6",
                "back": "Act of crowning Joshua"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 7",
                "back": "Hearts become like flint"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 8",
                "back": "Security comes to Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 9",
                "back": "Return of the Messiah"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 10",
                "back": "Ephraim and Judah restored"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 11",
                "back": "Teaching about wicked shepherds"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 12",
                "back": "Understanding whom they pierced"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 13",
                "back": "Refining of God's remnant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Zechariah 14",
                "back": "New kingdom ushered in"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Malachi": {
            "name": "Malachi",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Malachi 1",
                "back": "Lord reproves and reminds"
              },
              {
                "front": "Malachi 2",
                "back": "Offenses of the priests"
              },
              {
                "front": "Malachi 3",
                "back": "Robbing God is cursed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Malachi 4",
                "back": "Dawning of new day"
              }
            ]
          }
        }
      },
      "New Testament": {
        "name": "New Testament",
        "subcategories": {
          "Matthew": {
            "name": "Matthew",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Matthew 1",
                "back": "Genealogy of Jesus Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 2",
                "back": "Opposition of King Herod"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 3",
                "back": "Spirit's descent upon Jesus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 4",
                "back": "Power over Satan’s temptations"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 5",
                "back": "Expounding sermon on mount"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 6",
                "back": "Lessons on proper priorities (or Learn God is first)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 7",
                "back": "Outline for finding God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 8",
                "back": "Faithful centurion, healing others"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 9",
                "back": "Matthew's call from Jesus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 10",
                "back": "Apostles sent to preach"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 11",
                "back": "Testimony about John's message"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 12",
                "back": "True messiah called demonic"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 13",
                "back": "Hidden message of parables"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 14",
                "back": "Execution of John the Baptist"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 15",
                "back": "Wisdom in answering Pharisees"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 16",
                "back": "Key confession by Peter"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 17",
                "back": "Impact of Jesus' transfiguration"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 18",
                "back": "Need for true forgiveness"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 19",
                "back": "Grounds for divorce clarified"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 20",
                "back": "Opportunities in the vineyard"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 21",
                "back": "Fig tree is cursed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 22",
                "back": "Taxes paid to Caesar"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 23",
                "back": "Hypocrisy denounced by “woes”"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 24",
                "back": "Events of his coming"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 25",
                "back": "Jesus gives kingdom parables"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 26",
                "back": "Events on Calvary's eve"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 27",
                "back": "Way of the cross"
              },
              {
                "front": "Matthew 28",
                "back": "Savior's resurrection and commission"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Mark": {
            "name": "Mark",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Mark 1",
                "back": "Christ the working servant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 2",
                "back": "Healing of the paralytic"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 3",
                "back": "Rebuke of Unpardonable Sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 4",
                "back": "Illustration of the soils"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 5",
                "back": "Situation with Gadarenes, Jairus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 6",
                "back": "Taking care of the five thousand"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 7",
                "back": "Traditions of Pharisees attacked"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 8",
                "back": "Healing blind man at Bethsaida"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 9",
                "back": "Eagerness to be the greatest"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 10",
                "back": "Servant attitude is mandatory"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 11",
                "back": "Entry into Jerusalem triumphant"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 12",
                "back": "Resurrection queries are answered"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 13",
                "back": "Violent destruction of temple"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 14",
                "back": "Anguished prayer in Gethsemane"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 15",
                "back": "Narrative of Jesus' death"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mark 16",
                "back": "Tomb is found empty"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Luke": {
            "name": "Luke",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Luke 1",
                "back": "John named by Zacharias"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 2",
                "back": "Events during Jesus' childhood"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 3",
                "back": "Speech by John the Baptist"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 4",
                "back": "Undergoing rejection at Nazareth"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 5",
                "back": "Simon Peter follows Jesus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 6",
                "back": "Choosing the twelve disciples"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 7",
                "back": "Honest report to John"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 8",
                "back": "Rebuking wind and water"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 9",
                "back": "Instruction on cost of discipleship"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 10",
                "back": "Seventy P&R, good Samaritan, Mary & Martha"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 11",
                "back": "Teaching on prayer"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 12",
                "back": "Therefore do not worry"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 13",
                "back": "Healing on the Sabbath (also ch14)"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 14",
                "back": "Exalt self and be humbled"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 15",
                "back": "Prodigal son is received"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 16",
                "back": "Entrance into Abraham's bosom"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 17",
                "back": "Response of ten lepers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 18",
                "back": "Faithful persistence is rewarded"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 19",
                "back": "Eagerness of Zacchaeus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 20",
                "back": "Christ repeatedly outwits Pharisees"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 21",
                "back": "Two mites from widow"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 22",
                "back": "Mockery of the trial"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 23",
                "back": "Acceptance of penitent thief"
              },
              {
                "front": "Luke 24",
                "back": "News of Jesus' resurrection"
              }
            ]
          },
          "John": {
            "name": "John",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "John 1",
                "back": "Jesus is the Word"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 2",
                "back": "Overturning tables, wedding miracle"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 3",
                "back": "Heavenly rebirth confuses Nicodemus"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 4",
                "back": "Need of Samaritan woman"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 5",
                "back": "Testimony to Jesus' deity"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 6",
                "back": "Heavenly Bread of life"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 7",
                "back": "Exclamation at the feast"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 8",
                "back": "Grace for adulteress defended"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 9",
                "back": "Opposition to removing blindness"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 10",
                "back": "Shepherd and His sheep"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 11",
                "back": "Power/prayer to raise Lazarus"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 12",
                "back": "Eager anointing by Mary"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 13",
                "back": "Lessons at last supper"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 14",
                "back": "Offer of Holy Spirit"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 15",
                "back": "Fruit of the vine"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 16",
                "back": "Believer's comfort and joy"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 17",
                "back": "Extended prayer of Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 18",
                "back": "Lord's betrayal, arrest, denial"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 19",
                "back": "Illegal trials and crucifixion"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 20",
                "back": "Eyewitnesses to the resurrection"
              },
              {
                "front": "John 21",
                "back": "Final charge to Peter"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Acts": {
            "name": "Acts",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Acts 1",
                "back": "Heavenly ascension of Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 2",
                "back": "Outpouring of Holy Spirit"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 3",
                "back": "Lame man is healed"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 4",
                "back": "Yield from public preaching"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 5",
                "back": "Sapphira and Ananias judged"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 6",
                "back": "Providing deacons ends injustice"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 7",
                "back": "Illustrative defense by Stephen"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 8",
                "back": "Rising persecution, simony, Ethiopian"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 9",
                "back": "Introducing Saul to gospel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 10",
                "back": "Taking gospel to Cornelius"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 11",
                "back": "Worship with Gentiles defended"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 12",
                "back": "Outbreak from the prison"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 13",
                "back": "Relaying gospel to Antioch"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 14",
                "back": "Kindness mixed with confusion"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 15",
                "back": "Investigation by Jerusalem Council"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 16",
                "back": "Need for Timothy's circumcision"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 17",
                "back": "Gospel presented to Athens"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 18",
                "back": "Interview with Aquila, Priscilla"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 19",
                "back": "New believers in Ephesus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 20",
                "back": "Touching farewell from Ephesians"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 21",
                "back": "Holy Spirit warns Paul"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 22",
                "back": "Effect of Paul's testimony"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 23",
                "back": "Council of the Sanhedrin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 24",
                "back": "Hearing held by Felix"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 25",
                "back": "Urgent appeal to Caesar"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 26",
                "back": "Reasoning with King Agrippa"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 27",
                "back": "Caesarea to Malta Island"
              },
              {
                "front": "Acts 28",
                "back": "Heralding gospel in chains"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Romans": {
            "name": "Romans",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Romans 1",
                "back": "Turpitude of man unexcused"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 2",
                "back": "Human judgment of sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 3",
                "back": "Evidence of God's justification"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 4",
                "back": "God counts Abraham righteous"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 5",
                "back": "Obtaining righteousness by Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 6",
                "back": "Sinful nature is crucified"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 7",
                "back": "Problem of continued sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 8",
                "back": "Experiencing freedom in Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 9",
                "back": "Love shown for Israel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 10",
                "back": "Opportunity for Jew's salvation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 11",
                "back": "Fullness of the gentiles"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 12",
                "back": "Joy in using gifts"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 13",
                "back": "Established authorities of God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 14",
                "back": "Strong and weak brethren"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 15",
                "back": "Unity within the church"
              },
              {
                "front": "Romans 16",
                "back": "Salutations given by Paul"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Corinthians": {
            "name": "1 Corinthians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 1",
                "back": "Exhortation to Christian unity"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 2",
                "back": "Response of natural man"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 3",
                "back": "Reasons for Christian carnality"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 4",
                "back": "Observations on Paul's ministry"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 5",
                "back": "Rebuking immorality in the church"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 6",
                "back": "Sins against the body"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 7",
                "back": "Instructions for marriage partners"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 8",
                "back": "Never be a stumbling block"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 9",
                "back": "Believers must yield rights"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 10",
                "back": "Examples of fathers' lusting"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 11",
                "back": "Head coverings and communion"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 12",
                "back": "Abundance of Spirit giftings"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 13",
                "back": "Virtues of true love"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 14",
                "back": "Instructions on using tongues"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 15",
                "back": "Order in the resurrections"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Corinthians 16",
                "back": "Reminders about ministry helpers"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Corinthians": {
            "name": "2 Corinthians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 1",
                "back": "Testimony to Paul's sincerity"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 2",
                "back": "Heaviness of Paul's heart"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 3",
                "back": "Excellence of present ministry"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 4",
                "back": "Treasure in earthen vessels"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 5",
                "back": "Reconciliation offered to all"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 6",
                "back": "Union with unbelievers forbidden"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 7",
                "back": "Exhortation to perfecting holiness"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 8",
                "back": "Generosity of the Macedonians"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 9",
                "back": "Opportunity for cheerful giving"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 10",
                "back": "Spiritual authority of Paul"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 11",
                "back": "Paul's boastings in Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 12",
                "back": "Experience of Paul's thorn"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Corinthians 13",
                "back": "Lives that stand the test"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Galatians": {
            "name": "Galatians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Galatians 1",
                "back": "Turning from true gospel"
              },
              {
                "front": "Galatians 2",
                "back": "Hypocrisy of Peter’s actions"
              },
              {
                "front": "Galatians 3",
                "back": "Example of Abraham's faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "Galatians 4",
                "back": "Law versus liberty"
              },
              {
                "front": "Galatians 5",
                "back": "Attitudes from Spirit's leading"
              },
              {
                "front": "Galatians 6",
                "back": "Win back erring believers"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Ephesians": {
            "name": "Ephesians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Ephesians 1",
                "back": "Christ’s spiritual blessings given"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ephesians 2",
                "back": "Household of God reconciled"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ephesians 3",
                "back": "Understanding of the mystery"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ephesians 4",
                "back": "Reasons for spiritual gifts"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ephesians 5",
                "back": "Christ's example for marriage"
              },
              {
                "front": "Ephesians 6",
                "back": "Honor authorities, spiritual warfare"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Philippians": {
            "name": "Philippians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Philippians 1",
                "back": "Joy of Christian fellowship"
              },
              {
                "front": "Philippians 2",
                "back": "Outward evidences of humility"
              },
              {
                "front": "Philippians 3",
                "back": "Yearning to know Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "Philippians 4",
                "back": "Sufficiency of God's provisions"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Colossians": {
            "name": "Colossians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Colossians 1",
                "back": "Hope produced by Christ"
              },
              {
                "front": "Colossians 2",
                "back": "Objections to false teachers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Colossians 3",
                "back": "Principles for Christian living"
              },
              {
                "front": "Colossians 4",
                "back": "Expectant prayer and greetings"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Thessalonians": {
            "name": "1 Thessalonians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Thessalonians 1",
                "back": "Faith of Thessalonian church"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Thessalonians 2",
                "back": "Apostolic labors in Thessalonica"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Thessalonians 3",
                "back": "Investigation of church's wellbeing"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Thessalonians 4",
                "back": "True love between Christians"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Thessalonians 5",
                "back": "Hope in Christ's return"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Thessalonians": {
            "name": "2 Thessalonians",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Thessalonians 1",
                "back": "Description of Thessalonian's faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Thessalonians 2",
                "back": "Apostasy in last days"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Thessalonians 3",
                "back": "Yield fruit through work"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Timothy": {
            "name": "1 Timothy",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Timothy 1",
                "back": "Advice concerning false teachings"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Timothy 2",
                "back": "Directions for prayer, women"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Timothy 3",
                "back": "Virtues of Christian elders"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Timothy 4",
                "back": "Instruction for godly living"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Timothy 5",
                "back": "Counsel concerning the widows"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Timothy 6",
                "back": "Effects of worldly living"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Timothy": {
            "name": "2 Timothy",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Timothy 1",
                "back": "Hold on to true faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Timothy 2",
                "back": "Obey and teach the word"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Timothy 3",
                "back": "Last days bring apostasy"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Timothy 4",
                "back": "Diligently preach God's word"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Titus": {
            "name": "Titus",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Titus 1",
                "back": "Sound doctrine silences error"
              },
              {
                "front": "Titus 2",
                "back": "Order life to doctrine"
              },
              {
                "front": "Titus 3",
                "back": "Never shun good deeds"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Philemon": {
            "name": "Philemon",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Philemon 43472",
                "back": "Letter of Philemon's love"
              },
              {
                "front": "Philemon 43691",
                "back": "Onesimus becomes a Christian"
              },
              {
                "front": "Philemon 15-20",
                "back": "Vindication requested for Onesimus"
              },
              {
                "front": "Philemon 21-25",
                "back": "Expectation cited by Paul"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Hebrews": {
            "name": "Hebrews",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 1",
                "back": "Nature of God's Son"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 2",
                "back": "Exaltation after Christ's sacrifice"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 3",
                "back": "Worthy of man's obedience"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 4",
                "back": "Promise of believers' rest"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 5",
                "back": "Remember Christ like Melchizedek"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 6",
                "back": "Inheritance for persistent faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 7",
                "back": "Eternal priesthood for Melchizedek"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 8",
                "back": "Second covenant supersedes first"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 9",
                "back": "Testimonies of Christ's blood"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 10",
                "back": "Holiness through one sacrifice"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 11",
                "back": "Obedience of God's faithful"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 12",
                "back": "Obedience helped by discipline"
              },
              {
                "front": "Hebrews 13",
                "back": "Duties of the Christian"
              }
            ]
          },
          "James": {
            "name": "James",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "James 1",
                "back": "Working patience through trials"
              },
              {
                "front": "James 2",
                "back": "Obedience that accompanies faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "James 3",
                "back": "Restraining the unbridled tongue"
              },
              {
                "front": "James 4",
                "back": "Keeping calm in conflicts"
              },
              {
                "front": "James 5",
                "back": "Suffering and sick saints"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 Peter": {
            "name": "1 Peter",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Peter 1",
                "back": "Trials prove your faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Peter 2",
                "back": "Respond like Christ's example"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Peter 3",
                "back": "Innocent conscience quiets foes"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Peter 4",
                "back": "Attitudes pleasing to God"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Peter 5",
                "back": "Leaders to serve humbly"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Peter": {
            "name": "2 Peter",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Peter 1",
                "back": "Add virtue to faith"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Peter 2",
                "back": "Deeds of false teachers"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Peter 3",
                "back": "Diligence before the Lord's return"
              }
            ]
          },
          "1 John": {
            "name": "1 John",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 John 1",
                "back": "Living in the light"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 John 2",
                "back": "Importance of our advocate"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 John 3",
                "back": "God’s children avoid sin"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 John 4",
                "back": "How Christians should love"
              },
              {
                "front": "1 John 5",
                "back": "True witness in believers"
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 John": {
            "name": "2 John",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 John 43469",
                "back": "Greetings to brother Gaius"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 John 43591",
                "back": "Accept strangers and brethren"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 John 43654",
                "back": "Invest in God's work"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 John 43718",
                "back": "Unflattering words about Diotrephes"
              },
              {
                "front": "2 John 43783",
                "back": "Special thanks to Demetrius"
              }
            ]
          },
          "3 John": {
            "name": "3 John",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "3 John 43469",
                "back": "Greetings to brother Gaius"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 John 43591",
                "back": "Accept strangers and brethren"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 John 43654",
                "back": "Invest in God's work"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 John 43718",
                "back": "Unflattering words about Diotrephes"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 John 43783",
                "back": "Special thanks to Demetrius"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Jude": {
            "name": "Jude",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Jude 43469",
                "back": "Jude warns against apostasy"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jude 43592",
                "back": "Unbelief seen throughout history"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jude 43696",
                "back": "Description of false teachers"
              },
              {
                "front": "Jude 20-25",
                "back": "Exhortation to stay faithful"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Revelation": {
            "name": "Revelation",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Revelation 1",
                "back": "Patmos vision of John"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 2",
                "back": "Rebuke for four churches"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 3",
                "back": "Other three churches rebuked"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 4",
                "back": "Picture of God's throne"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 5",
                "back": "Holy Lamb is worshiped"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 6",
                "back": "Each seal is broken"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 7",
                "back": "Crowd coming from tribulation"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 8",
                "back": "Yoke of four trumpets"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 9",
                "back": "Abyss releases more trumpets"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 10",
                "back": "Book eaten by John"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 11",
                "back": "Opposition to two witnesses"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 12",
                "back": "Unrelenting opposition of dragon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 13",
                "back": "Tatoo of world ruler"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 14",
                "back": "Time ripe for harvest"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 15",
                "back": "Harps played for God"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 16",
                "back": "Emptying of the bowls"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 17",
                "back": "Future destruction of Babylon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 18",
                "back": "Utter desolation of Babylon"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 19",
                "back": "Triumphant feast of the Lamb"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 20",
                "back": "Ultimate resurrection and judgment"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 21",
                "back": "Revelation of New Jerusalem"
              },
              {
                "front": "Revelation 22",
                "back": "Eternal city and words"
              }
            ]
          }
        }
      },
      "Book of Mormon": {
        "name": "Book of Mormon",
        "subcategories": {
          "1 Nephi": {
            "name": "1 Nephi",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 1",
                "back": "Nephi begins the record – Lehi sees in vision a pillar of fire, and prophesies the destruction of Jerusalem ~600 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 2",
                "back": "Lehi takes his family into the wilderness– Laman/Lemuel murmur – Nephi sees Lord. ~600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 3",
                "back": "Lehi’s sons return to obtain the plates–  Laman and Lemuel smite Nephi and are reproved by an angel. ~ 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 4",
                "back": "Nephi slays Laban –  Zoram chooses to join Lehi’s family.  Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 5",
                "back": "Sariah & Lehi rejoice over son's return – The plates contain writings of Moses – Lehi a descendant of Joseph ~ 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 6",
                "back": "Nephi writes that his purpose is to persuade men to come unto God  ~600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 7",
                "back": "Sons return to Jerusalem for family of Ishmael – Laman and others bind Nephi with cords. ~600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 8",
                "back": "Lehi sees a vision of the tree of life–  Sariah, Nephi, and Sam partake of fruit–  Laman and Lemuel refuse. ~600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 9",
                "back": "Nephi makes two sets of records– The larger plates are a secular history; the smaller contain sacred things. ~600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 10",
                "back": "Lehi tells of the coming among the Jews of a Messiah, a Savior, a Redeemer– He tells also of the coming of the one who should baptize the Lamb of God– Lehi tells of the death and resurrection of the Messiah– He compares the scattering and gathering of Israel to an olive tree– Nephi speaks of the Son of God, of the gift of the Holy Ghost, and of the need for righteousness. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 11",
                "back": "Nephi sees the Spirit of the Lord and is shown in vision the tree of life– He sees the mother of the Son of God and learns of the condescension of God– He sees the baptism, ministry, and crucifixion of the Lamb of God– He sees also the call and ministry of the twelve apostles of the Lamb. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 12",
                "back": "Nephi sees in vision: the land of promise; the righteousness, iniquity, and downfall of its inhabitants; the coming of the Lamb of God among them; how the twelve disciples and the twelve apostles shall judge Israel; the loathsome and filthy state of those who dwindle in unbelief. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 13",
                "back": "Nephi sees in vision: the church of the devil set up among the Gentiles; the discovery and colonizing of America; the loss of many plain and precious parts of the Bible; the resultant state of gentile apostasy; the restoration of the gospel, the coming forth of latter– day scripture, and the building up of Zion. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 14",
                "back": "An angel tells Nephi of the blessings and cursings to fall upon the Gentiles– There are only two churches: the Church of the Lamb of God and the church of the devil– The saints of God in all nations are persecuted by the great and abominable church– The apostle John shall write concerning the end of the world. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 15",
                "back": "Lehi’s seed are to receive the gospel from the Gentiles in the latter days– The gathering of Israel is likened unto an olive tree whose natural branches shall be grafted in again– Nephi interprets the vision of the tree of life and speaks of the justice of God in dividing the wicked from the righteous. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 16",
                "back": "The wicked take the truth to be hard– Lehi’s sons marry the daughters of Ishmael– The Liahona guides their course in the wilderness– Messages from the Lord are written on the Liahona from time to time– Ishmael dies; his family murmur because of afflictions. Between 600 and 592 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 17",
                "back": "Nephi is commanded to build a ship– His brethren oppose him– He exhorts them by recounting the history of God’s dealings with Israel– He is filled with the power of God– His brethren are forbidden to touch him, lest they whither as a dried reed. About 592– 591 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 18",
                "back": "The ship is finished– The births of Jacob and Joseph are mentioned– The company embarks for the promised land– The sons of Ishmael and their wives join in revelry and rebellion– Nephi is bound, and the ship is driven back by a terrible tempest– Nephi is freed, and by his prayer the storm ceases– They arrive in the promised land. About 590– 589 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 19",
                "back": "Nephi makes plates of ore and records the history of his people– The God of Israel shall come six hundred years from the time Lehi left Jerusalem– Nephi tells of His sufferings and crucifixion– The Jews shall be despised and scattered until the latter days, when they will return unto the Lord. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 20",
                "back": "The Lord reveals his purposes to Israel– They have been chosen in the furnace of affliction and are to go forth from Babylon– Compare Isaiah 48. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 21",
                "back": "Messiah shall be a light to the Gentiles and shall free the prisoners– Israel shall be gathered with power in the last days– Kings shall be their nursing fathers– Compare Isaiah 49. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "1 Nephi 22",
                "back": "Israel shall be scattered upon all the face of the earth– The gentiles shall nurse and nourish Israel with the gospel in the last days– Israel shall be gathered and saved, and the wicked shall burn as stubble– The kingdom of the devil shall be destroyed, and Satan shall be bound. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "2 Nephi": {
            "name": "2 Nephi",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 1",
                "back": "Lehi prophesies of a land of liberty– His seed shall be scattered and smitten if they reject the Holy One of Israel– He exhorts his sons to put on the armor of righteousness. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 2",
                "back": "Redemption cometh through the Holy Messiah– Freedom of choice (agency) is essential to existence and progression– Adam fell that men might be– Men are free to choose liberty and eternal life. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 3",
                "back": "Joseph in Egypt saw the Nephites in vision– He prophesied of Joseph Smith, the latter– day seer; of Moses, who would deliver Israel; and of the coming forth of the Book of Mormon. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 4",
                "back": "Lehi counsels and blesses his posterity– He dies and is buried– Nephi glories in the goodness of God to him– Nephi puts his trust in the Lord forever. Between 588 and 570 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 5",
                "back": "The Nephites separate themselves from the Lamanites, keep the law of Moses, and build a temple– Because of their unbelief, the Lamanites are cursed, receive a skin of blackness, and become a scourge unto the Nephites. Between 588 and 559 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 6",
                "back": "Jacob recounts Jewish history: Their Babylonian captivity and return; the ministry and crucifixion of the Holy One of Israel; the help received from the gentiles; and their latter– day restoration when they believe in the Messiah. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 7",
                "back": "Isaiah speaks Messianically– Messiah shall have the tongue of the learned– He shall give his back to the smiters– He shall not be confounded– Compare Isaiah 50. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 8",
                "back": "In the last days, the Lord shall comfort Zion and gather Israel– The redeemed shall come to Zion amid great joy– Compare Isaiah 51 and 52:1– 2. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 9",
                "back": "Jews shall be gathered in all their lands of promise– Atonement ransoms man from the fall– The bodies of the dead shall come forth from the grave, and their spirits from hell and from paradise– They shall be judged– Atonement saves from death, hell, the devil, and endless torment– The righteous to be saved in the kingdom of God– Penalties for sins set forth– The Holy One of Israel is the keeper of the gate. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 10",
                "back": "Jews shall crucify their God– They shall be scattered until they begin to believe in him– America shall be a land of liberty where no king shall rule– Be reconciled to God and gain salvation through his grace. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 11",
                "back": "Jacob saw his Redeemer– The law of Moses typifies Christ and proves he shall come. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 12",
                "back": "Isaiah sees the latter– day temple, gathering of Israel, and millennial judgment and peace– The proud and wicked shall be brought low at the Second Coming– Compare Isaiah 2. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 13",
                "back": "Judah and Jerusalem shall be punished for their disobedience– The Lord pleads for and judges his people– The daughters of Zion are cursed and tormented for their worldliness– Compare Isaiah 3. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 14",
                "back": "Zion and her daughters shall be redeemed and cleansed in the millennial day– Compare Isaiah 4. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 15",
                "back": "The Lord’s vineyard (Israel) shall become desolate and his people shall be scattered– Woes shall come upon them in their apostate and scattered state– The Lord shall lift an ensign and gather Israel– Compare Isaiah 5. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 16",
                "back": "Isaiah sees the Lord– Isaiah’s sins are forgiven– He is called to prophesy– He prophesies of the rejection by the Jews of Christ’s teachings– A remnant shall return– Compare Isaiah 6. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 17",
                "back": "Ephraim and Syria wage war against Judah– Christ shall be born of a virgin– Compare Isaiah 7. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 18",
                "back": "Christ shall be as a stone of stumbling and a rock of offense– Seek the Lord, not peeping wizards– Turn to the law and to the testimony for guidance– Compare Isaiah 8. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 19",
                "back": "Isaiah speaks Messianically– The people in darkness to see a great Light– Unto us a child is born– He shall be the Prince of Peace and shall reign on David’s throne– Compare Isaiah 9. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 20",
                "back": "Destruction of Assyria is a type of destruction of wicked at the Second Coming– Few people shall be left after the Lord comes again– Remnant of Jacob shall return in that day– Compare Isaiah 10. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 21",
                "back": "Stem of Jesse (Christ) shall judge in righteousness– The knowledge of God shall cover the earth in the Millennium– The Lord shall raise an ensign and gather Israel– Compare Isaiah 11. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 22",
                "back": "In the millennial day all men shall praise the Lord– He shall dwell among them– Compare Isaiah 12. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 23",
                "back": "Destruction of Babylon is a type of destruction at Second Coming– It shall be a day of wrath and vengeance– Babylon (the world) shall fall forever– Compare Isaiah 13. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 24",
                "back": "Israel shall be gathered and shall enjoy millennial rest– Lucifer cast out of heaven for rebellion– Israel shall triumph over Babylon (the world)– Compare Isaiah 14. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 25",
                "back": "Nephi glories in plainness– Isaiah’s prophecies shall be understood in the last days– The Jews shall return from Babylon, crucify the Messiah, and be scattered and scourged– They shall be restored when they believe in the Messiah– He shall first come six hundred years after Lehi left Jerusalem– Nephites keep the law of Moses and believe in Christ, who is the Holy One of Israel. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 26",
                "back": "Christ shall minister to the Nephites– Nephi foresees the destruction of his people– They shall speak from the dust– The gentiles shall build up false churches and secret combinations– The Lord forbids men to practice priestcraft. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 27",
                "back": "Darkness and apostasy shall cover the earth in the last days– The Book of Mormon shall come forth– Three witnesses shall testify of the book– The learned man cannot read the sealed book– The Lord shall do a marvelous work and a wonder– Compare Isaiah 29. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 28",
                "back": "Many false churches shall be built up in the last days– They shall teach false and vain and foolish doctrines– Apostasy shall abound because of false teachers– The devil shall rage in the hearts of men– He shall teach all manner of false doctrines. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 29",
                "back": "Many gentiles shall reject the Book of Mormon– They shall say: We need no more Bible– The Lord speaks to many nations– He will judge the world out of the books thus written. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 30",
                "back": "Converted gentiles shall be numbered with the covenant people– Many Lamanites and Jews shall believe the word and become a delightsome people– Israel shall be restored and the wicked destroyed. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 31",
                "back": "Nephi tells why Christ was baptized– Men must follow Christ, be baptized, receive the Holy Ghost, and endure to the end to be saved– Repentance and baptism are the gate to the strait and narrow path– Eternal life comes to those who keep the commandments after baptism. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 32",
                "back": "Angels speak by the power of the Holy Ghost– Men must pray and gain knowledge for themselves from the Holy Ghost. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "2 Nephi 33",
                "back": "Nephi’s words are true– They testify of Christ– Those who believe in Christ will believe Nephi’s words– They shall stand as a witness before the judgment bar. Between 559 and 545 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Jacob": {
            "name": "Jacob",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Jacob 1",
                "back": "Jacob and Joseph seek to persuade men to believe in Christ and keep his commandments– Nephi dies– Wickedness prevails among the Nephites. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Jacob 2",
                "back": "Jacob denounces the love of riches, pride, and unchastity– Men should seek riches to help their fellow men– Jacob condemns the unauthorized practice of plural marriage– The Lord delights in the chastity of women. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Jacob 3",
                "back": "The pure in heart receive the pleasing word of God– Lamanite righteousness exceeds that of Nephites– Jacob warns against fornication, lasciviousness, and every sin. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Jacob 4",
                "back": "All the prophets worshipped the Father in the name of Christ– Abraham’s offering of Isaac was in similitude of God and his Only Begotten– Men should reconcile themselves to God through the atonement– The Jews shall reject the foundation stone. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Jacob 5",
                "back": "Jacob quotes Zenos relative to the allegory of the tame and wild olive trees– They are a likeness of Israel and the gentiles– The scattering and gathering of Israel are prefigured– Allusions are made to the Nephites and Lamanites and all the house of Israel– Gentiles shall be grafted into Israel– Eventually the vineyard shall be burned. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Jacob 6",
                "back": "The Lord shall recover Israel in the last days– Then the world shall be burned with fire– Men must follow Christ to avoid the lake of fire and brimstone. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Jacob 7",
                "back": "Sherem denies Christ, contends with Jacob, demands a sign, and is smitten of God– All of the prophets have spoken of Christ and his atonement– The Nephites lived out their days as wanderers, born in tribulation, and hated by the Lamanites. Between 544 and 421 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Enos": {
            "name": "Enos",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Enos 1",
                "back": "Enos prays mightily and gains a remission of his sins– The voice of the Lord comes into his mind promising salvation for the Lamanites in a future day– Nephites sought to reclaim the Lamanites in their day– Enos rejoices in his Redeemer. Between 544 and 420 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Jarom": {
            "name": "Jarom",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Jarom 1",
                "back": "The Nephites keep the law of Moses, look forward to the coming of Christ, and prosper in the land– Many prophets labor to keep them in the way of truth. Between 420 and 361 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Omni": {
            "name": "Omni",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Omni 1",
                "back": "Omni, Amaron, Chemish, Abinadom, and Amaleki, each in turn, keep the records– Mosiah discovers the people of Zarahemla who came from Jerusalem in the days of Zedekiah– He is made king over them– The Mulekites had discovered Coriantumr, the last of the Jaredites– King Benjamin succeeds Mosiah– Men should offer their souls as an offering to Christ. Between 361 and 130 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Words of Mormon": {
            "name": "Words of Mormon",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Words of Mormon 1",
                "back": "Mormon abridges their history onto the plates of Mormon– He inserts the plates of Nephi into the abridgement– King Benjamin establishes peace in the land. About A.D. 385"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Mosiah": {
            "name": "Mosiah",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 1",
                "back": "King Benjamin teaches his sons the language and prophecies of their fathers– Their religion and civilization have been preserved because of the records kept on the various plates– Mosiah is chosen as king and is given custody of the records and other things. About 130– 124 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 2",
                "back": "King Benjamin addresses his people– He recounts the equity, fairness, and spirituality of his reign– He counsels them to serve their heavenly King– Those who rebel against God shall suffer anguish like unquenchable fire. About 124 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 3",
                "back": "King Benjamin continues his address– The Lord Omnipotent shall minister among men in a tabernacle of clay– Blood shall come from every pore as he atones for the sins of the world– His is the only name whereby salvation comes– Men can put off the natural man and become saints through the atonement– The torment of the wicked shall be as a lake of fire and brimstone. About 124 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 4",
                "back": "King Benjamin continues his address– Salvation comes because of the atonement– Believe in God to be saved– Retain a remission of your sins through faithfulness– Impart of your substance to the poor– Do all things in wisdom and order. About 124 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 5",
                "back": "The saints become the sons and daughters of Christ through faith– They are then called by the name of Christ– King Benjamin exhorts them to be steadfast and immovable in good works. About 124 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 6",
                "back": "King Benjamin records the names of the people and appoints priests to teach them– Mosiah reigns as a righteous king. About 124– 121 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 7",
                "back": "Ammon finds the land of Lehi– Nephi where Limhi is king– Limhi’s people are in bondage to the Lamanites– Limhi recounts their history– A prophet (Abinadi) had testified that Christ is the God and Father of all things– Those who sow filthiness reap the whirlwind, and those who put their trust in the Lord shall be delivered. About 121 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 8",
                "back": "Ammon teaches the people of Limhi– He learns of the twenty– four Jaredite plates– Ancient records can be translated by seers– The gift of seership exceeds all others. About 121 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 9",
                "back": "Zeniff leads a group from Zarahemla to possess the land of Lehi– Nephi– The Lamanite king permits them to inherit the land– There is war between the Lamanites and Zeniff’s people. About 200– 187 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 10",
                "back": "King Laman dies– His people are wild and ferocious and believe in false traditions– Zeniff and his people prevail against them. About 178– 160 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 11",
                "back": "King Noah rules in wickedness– He revels in riotous living with his wives and concubines– Abinadi prophesies that the people will be taken into bondage– His life is sought by King Noah. Between 160 and 150 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 12",
                "back": "Abinadi is imprisoned for prophesying the destruction of the people and the death of King Noah– The false priests quote the scriptures and pretend to keep the law of Moses– Abinadi begins to teach them the Ten Commandments. About 148 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 13",
                "back": "Abinadi is protected by divine power– He teaches the Ten Commandments– Salvation does not come by the law of Moses alone– God himself shall make an atonement and redeem his people. About 148 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 14",
                "back": "Isaiah speaks Messianically– Messiah’s humiliation and sufferings are set forth– He makes his soul an offering for sin and makes intercession for transgressors– Compare Isaiah 53. About 148 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 15",
                "back": "How Christ is both the Father and the Son– He shall make intercession and bear the transgressions of his people– They and all the holy prophets are his seed– He bringeth to pass the resurrection– Little children have eternal life. About 148 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 16",
                "back": "God redeems men from their lost and fallen state– Those who are carnal remain as though there was no redemption– Christ brings to pass a resurrection to endless life or to endless damnation. About 148 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 17",
                "back": "Alma believes and writes the words of Abinadi– Abinadi suffers death by fire– He prophesies disease and death by fire upon his murderers. About 148 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 18",
                "back": "Alma preaches in private– He sets forth the covenant of baptism and baptizes at the waters of Mormon– He organizes the Church of Christ and ordains priests– They support themselves and teach the people– Alma and his people flee from King Noah into the wilderness. About 148– 145 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 19",
                "back": "Gideon seeks to slay King Noah– The Lamanites invade the land– King Noah suffers death by fire– Limhi rules as a tributary monarch. Between 145 and 122 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 20",
                "back": "Lamanite daughters are abducted by the priests of Noah– The Lamanites wage war upon Limhi and his people– They are repulsed and pacified. Between 145 and 122 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 21",
                "back": "Limhi’s people are smitten and defeated by the Lamanites– They meet Ammon and are converted– They tell Ammon of the twenty– four Jaredite plates. Between 145 and 121 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 22",
                "back": "Plans are made for the people to escape from Lamanite bondage– The Lamanites are made drunk– The people escape, return to Zarahemla, and become subject to King Mosiah. About 121 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 23",
                "back": "Alma refuses to be king– He serves as high priest– The Lord chastens his people, and the Lamanites conquer the land of Helam– Amulon, leader of King Noah’s wicked priests, rules subject to the Lamanite monarch. Between 145 and 121 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 24",
                "back": "Amulon persecutes Alma and his people– They are to be put to death if they pray– The Lord makes their burdens seem light– He delivers them from bondage, and they return to Zarahemla. Between 145 and 120 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 25",
                "back": "The people (the Mulekites) of Zarahemla become Nephites– They learn of the people of Alma and of Zeniff– Alma baptizes Limhi and all his people– Mosiah authorizes Alma to organize the Church of God. About 120 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 26",
                "back": "Many members of the Church are led into sin by unbelievers– Alma is promised eternal life– Those who repent and are baptized gain forgiveness– Church members in sin who repent and confess to Alma and to the Lord shall be forgiven; otherwise they shall be excommunicated. Probably between 120 and 100 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 27",
                "back": "Mosiah forbids persecution and enjoins equality– Alma the younger and the four sons of Mosiah seek to destroy the Church– An angel appears and commands them to cease their evil course– Alma is struck dumb– All mankind must be born again to gain salvation– Alma and the sons of Mosiah declare glad tidings. Probably between 100 and 92 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 28",
                "back": "The sons of Mosiah shall have eternal life– They go to preach to the Lamanites– Mosiah translates the Jaredite plates with the two seer stones. About 92 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Mosiah 29",
                "back": "Mosiah proposes that judges be chosen in place of a king– Unrighteous kings lead their people into sin– Alma the younger is chosen chief judge by the voice of the people– He is also the high priest over the Church– Alma the elder and Mosiah die. About 92– 91 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Alma": {
            "name": "Alma",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Alma 1",
                "back": "Nehor teaches false doctrines, establishes a church, introduces priestcraft, and slays Gideon– He is executed for his crimes– Priestcrafts and persecutions spread among the people– The priests support themselves, the people care for the poor, and the Church prospers. About 91– 90 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 2",
                "back": "Amlici seeks to be king and is rejected by the voice of the people– His followers make him king– The Amlicites make war on the Nephites and are defeated– The Lamanites and Amlicites join forces and are defeated– Alma slays Amlici. 87 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 3",
                "back": "The Amlicites had marked themselves according to the prophetic word– The Lamanites had been cursed for their rebellion– Men bring their own curses upon themselves– The Nephites defeat another Lamanite army. 87 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 4",
                "back": "Alma baptizes thousands of converts– Iniquity enters the Church, and the Church’s progress is hindered– Nephihah is appointed chief judge– Alma, as high priest, devotes himself to the ministry. Between 86 and 83 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 5",
                "back": "To gain salvation, men must repent and keep the commandments, be born again, cleanse their garments through the blood of Christ, be humble and strip themselves from pride and envy, and do the works of righteousness– The Good Shepherd calleth his people– Those who do evil works are children of the devil– Alma testifies of the truth of his doctrine and commands men to repent– Names of the righteous shall be written in the book of life. About 83 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 6",
                "back": "The Church in Zarahemla is cleansed and set in order– Alma goes to Gideon to preach. About 83 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 7",
                "back": "Christ shall be born of Mary– He shall loose the bands of death and bear the sins of his people– Those who repent, are baptized, and keep the commandments shall have eternal life– Filthiness cannot inherit the kingdom of God– Humility, faith, hope, and charity are required. About 83 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 8",
                "back": "Alma preaches and baptizes in Melek– He is rejected in Ammonihah and leaves– An angel commands him to return and cry repentance unto the people– He is received by Amulek, and the two of them preach in Ammonihah. About 82 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 9",
                "back": "Alma commands the people of Ammonihah to repent– The Lord will be merciful to the Lamanites in the last days– If the Nephites forsake the light, they shall be destroyed by the Lamanites– The Son of God soon cometh– He shall redeem those who repent and are baptized and have faith in his name. About 82 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 10",
                "back": "Lehi descended from Manasseh– Amulek recounts the angelic command that he care for Alma– The prayers of the righteous cause the people to be spared– Unrighteous lawyers and judges lay the foundation of the destruction of the people. About 82 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 11",
                "back": "Nephite coinage set forth– Amulek contends with Zeezrom– Christ will not save people in their sins– Only those who inherit the kingdom of heaven are saved– All men shall rise in immortality– There is no death after the resurrection. About 82 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 12",
                "back": "Alma contends with Zeezrom– The mysteries of God can be given only to the faithful– Men are judged by their thoughts, beliefs, words, and works– The wicked shall suffer a spiritual death– This mortal life is a probationary state– The plan of redemption brings to pass the resurrection and, through faith, a remission of sins– The repentant have a claim on mercy through the Only Begotten Son. About 82 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 13",
                "back": "Men are called as high priests because of their exceeding faith and good works– They are to teach the commandments– Through righteousness they are sanctified and enter into the rest of the Lord– Melchizedek was one of these– Angels are declaring glad tidings throughout the land– They will reveal the actual coming of Christ. About 82 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 14",
                "back": "Alma and Amulek are imprisoned and smitten– The believers and their holy scriptures are burned by fire– These martyrs are received by the Lord in glory– The prison walls are rent and fall– Alma and Amulek are delivered and their persecutors are slain. About 82– 81 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 15",
                "back": "Alma and Amulek go to Sidom and establish a church– Alma heals Zeezrom, who joins the Church– Many are baptized and the Church prospers– Alma and Amulek go to Zarahemla. About 81 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 16",
                "back": "The Lamanites destroy the people of Ammonihah– Zoram leads the Nephites to victory over the Lamanites– Alma and Amulek and many others preach the word– They teach that after his resurrection Christ will appear to the Nephites. About 81– 78 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 17",
                "back": "The sons of Mosiah have the spirit of prophecy and of revelation– They go their several ways to declare the word to the Lamanites– Ammon goes to the land of Ishmael and becomes the servant of King Lamoni– Ammon saves the king’s flocks and slays his enemies at the waters of Sebus. From about 91 to 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 18",
                "back": "King Lamoni supposes that Ammon is the Great Spirit– Ammon teaches the king of the creation, of God’s dealings with men, and of the redemption that comes through Christ– Lamoni believes and falls to the earth as if dead. About 90 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 19",
                "back": "Lamoni receives the light of everlasting life and sees the Redeemer– His household fall into a trance, and some see angels– Ammon is preserved miraculously– He baptizes many and establishes a church among them. About 90 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 20",
                "back": "The Lord sends Ammon to Middoni to deliver his imprisoned brethren– Ammon and Lamoni meet Lamoni’s father, who is king over all the land– Ammon compels the old king to approve the release of his brethren. About 90 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 21",
                "back": "Aaron teaches the Amalekites about Christ and his atonement– Aaron and his brethren are imprisoned in Middoni– After their deliverance they teach in the synagogues and make many converts– Lamoni grants religious freedom to the people in the land of Ishmael. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 22",
                "back": "Aaron teaches Lamoni’s father about the creation, the fall of Adam, and the plan of redemption through Christ– The king and all his household are converted– How the land was divided between the Nephites and the Lamanites. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 23",
                "back": "Religious freedom is proclaimed– The Lamanites in seven lands and cities are converted– They call themselves Anti– Nephi– Lehies and are freed from the curse– The Amalekites and the Amulonites reject the truth. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 24",
                "back": "The Lamanites come against the people of God– The Anti– Nephi– Lehies rejoice in Christ and are visited by angels– They choose to suffer death rather than to defend themselves– More Lamanites are converted. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 25",
                "back": "Lamanite aggressions spread– The seed of the priests of Noah perish as Abinadi prophesied– Many Lamanites are converted and join the people of Anti– Nephi– Lehi– They believe in Christ and keep the law of Moses. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 26",
                "back": "Ammon glories in the Lord– The faithful are strengthened by the Lord and are given knowledge– By faith men may bring thousands of souls unto repentance– God has all power and comprehendeth all things. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 27",
                "back": "The Lord commands Ammon to lead the people of Anti– Nephi– Lehi to safety– Upon meeting Alma, Ammon’s joy exhausts his strength– The Nephites give them the land of Jershon– They are called the people of Ammon. Between 90 and 77 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 28",
                "back": "The Lamanites are defeated in a tremendous battle– Tens of thousands are slain– The wicked are consigned to a state of endless woe; the righteous attain a never– ending happiness. About 76 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 29",
                "back": "Alma desires to cry repentance with angelic zeal– The Lord grants teachers for all nations– Alma glories in the Lord’s work and in the success of Ammon and his brethren. About 76 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 30",
                "back": "Korihor, the antichrist, ridicules Christ, the atonement, and the spirit of prophecy– He teaches that there is no God, no fall of man, no penalty for sin, and no Christ– Alma testifies that Christ shall come and that all things denote there is a God– Korihor demands a sign and is struck dumb– The devil had appeared to Korihor as an angel and taught him what to say– He is trodden down and dies. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 31",
                "back": "Alma heads a mission to reclaim the apostate Zoramites– The Zoramites deny Christ, believe in a false concept of election, and worship with set prayers– The missionaries are filled with the Holy Spirit– Their afflictions are swallowed up in the joy of Christ. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 32",
                "back": "Alma teaches the poor whose afflictions had humbled them– Faith is a hope in that which is not seen which is true– Alma testifies that angels minister to men, women, and children– Alma compares the word unto a seed– It must be planted and nourished– Then it grows into a tree from which the fruit of eternal life is picked. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 33",
                "back": "Zenos taught that men should pray and worship in all places, and that judgments are turned away because of the Son– Zenock taught that mercy is bestowed because of the Son– Moses had lifted up in the wilderness a type of the Son of God. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 34",
                "back": "Amulek testifies that the word is in Christ unto salvation– Unless an atonement is made, all mankind must perish– The whole law of Moses points toward the sacrifice of the Son of God– The eternal plan of redemption is based on faith and repentance– Pray for temporal and spiritual blessings– This life is the time for men to prepare to meet God– Work out your salvation with fear and trembling. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 35",
                "back": "The preaching of the word destroys the craft of the Zoramites– They expel the converts, who then join the people of Ammon in Jershon– Alma sorrows because of the wickedness of the people. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 36",
                "back": "Alma testifies to Helaman of his conversion by an angel– He suffered the pains of a damned soul; he called upon the name of Jesus, and was then born of God– Sweet joy filled his soul– He saw concourses of angels praising God– His converts have tasted and seen as he did. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 37",
                "back": "The plates of brass and other scriptures are preserved to bring souls to salvation– The Jaredites were destroyed because of their wickedness– Their secret oaths and covenants must be kept from the people– Counsel with the Lord in all thy doings– As the Liahona guided the Nephites, so the word of Christ leads men to eternal life. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 38",
                "back": "Shiblon was persecuted for righteousness’ sake– Salvation is in Christ, who is the life and the light of the world– Bridle all your passions. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 39",
                "back": "Sexual sin is an abomination– Corianton’s sins kept the Zoramites from receiving the word– Christ’s redemption is retroactive in saving the faithful who preceded it. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 40",
                "back": "Christ bringeth to pass the resurrection of all men– The righteous dead go to paradise and the wicked to outer darkness to await the day of their resurrection– All things shall be restored to their proper and perfect frame in the resurrection. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 41",
                "back": "In the resurrection men come forth to a state of endless happiness or endless misery– Wickedness never was happiness– Carnal men are without God in the world– Every person receives again in the restoration the characteristics and attributes acquired in mortality. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 42",
                "back": "Mortality is a probationary time to enable man to repent and serve God– The fall brought temporal and spiritual death upon all mankind– Redemption comes through repentance– God himself atoneth for the sins of the world– Mercy is for those who repent– All others are subject to God’s justice– Mercy cometh because of the atonement– Only the truly penitent are saved. About 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 43",
                "back": "Alma and his sons preach the word– The Zoramites and other Nephite dissenters become Lamanites– The Lamanites come against the Nephites in war– Moroni arms the Nephites with defensive armor– The Lord reveals to Alma the strategy of the Lamanites– The Nephites defend their homes, liberties, families, and religion– The armies of Moroni and Lehi surround the Lamanites. About 74 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 44",
                "back": "Moroni commands the Lamanites to make a covenant of peace or be destroyed– Zerahemnah rejects the offer, and the battle resumes– Moroni’s armies defeat the Lamanites. About 74– 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 45",
                "back": "Helaman believes the words of Alma– Alma prophesies the destruction of the Nephites– He blesses and curses the land– Alma is taken up by the Spirit, even as Moses– Dissension grows in the Church. 73 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 46",
                "back": "Amalickiah conspires to be king– Moroni raises the title of liberty– He rallies the people to defend their religion– True believers are called Christians– A remnant of Joseph shall be preserved– Amalickiah and the dissenters flee to the land of Nephi– Those who will not support the cause of freedom are put to death. Between 73 and 72 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 47",
                "back": "Amalickiah uses treachery, murder, and intrigue to become king of the Lamanites– The Nephite dissenters are more wicked and ferocious than the Lamanites. 72 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 48",
                "back": "Amalickiah incites the Lamanites against the Nephites– Moroni prepares his people to defend the cause of the Christians– He rejoiced in liberty and freedom and was a mighty man of God. 72 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 49",
                "back": "The invading Lamanites are unable to take the fortified cities of Ammonihah and Noah– Amalickiah curses God and swears to drink the blood of Moroni– Helaman and his brethren continue to strengthen the Church. 72 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 50",
                "back": "Moroni fortifies the lands of the Nephites– They build many new cities– Wars and destructions befell the Nephites in the days of their wickedness and abominations– Morianton and his dissenters are defeated by Teancum– Nephihah dies and his son Pahoran fills the judgment– seat. About 72– 67 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 51",
                "back": "The king– men seek to change the law and set up a king– Pahoran and the freemen are supported by the voice of the people– Moroni compels the king– men to defend their liberty or be put to death– Amalickiah and the Lamanites capture many fortified cities– Teancum repels the Lamanite invasion and slays Amalickiah in his tent. About 67 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 52",
                "back": "Ammoron succeeds Amalickiah as king of the Lamanites– Moroni, Teancum, and Lehi lead the Nephites in a victorious war against the Lamanites– The city of Mulek is retaken, and Jacob the Lamanite is slain. About 66– 64 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 53",
                "back": "The Lamanite prisoners are used to fortify the city Bountiful– Dissensions among the Nephites give rise to Lamanite victories– Helaman takes command of the two thousand stripling sons of the people of Ammon. About 64 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 54",
                "back": "Ammoron and Moroni negotiate for the exchange of prisoners– Moroni demands that the Lamanites withdraw and cease their murderous attacks– Ammoron demands that the Nephites lay down their arms and become subject to the Lamanites. About 63 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 55",
                "back": "Moroni refuses to exchange prisoners– The Lamanite guards are enticed to become drunk, and the Nephite prisoners are freed– The city of Gid is taken without bloodshed. About 63 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 56",
                "back": "Helaman sends an epistle to Moroni recounting the state of the war with the Lamanites– Antipus and Helaman gain a great victory over the Lamanites– Helaman’s two thousand stripling sons fight with miraculous power and none of them are slain. About 66– 62 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 57",
                "back": "Helaman recounts the taking of Antiparah and the surrender and later the defense of Cumeni– His Ammonite striplings fight valiantly and all are wounded, but none are slain– Gid reports the slaying and the escape of the Lamanite prisoners. About 64– 63 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 58",
                "back": "Helaman, Gid, and Teomner take the city of Manti by a stratagem– The Lamanites withdraw– The sons of the people of Ammon are preserved as they stand fast in defense of their liberty and faith. About 63 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 59",
                "back": "Moroni asks Pahoran to strengthen the forces of Helaman– The Lamanites take the city of Nephihah– Moroni is angry with the government. About 62 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 60",
                "back": "Moroni complains to Pahoran of the government’s neglect of the armies– The Lord suffers the righteous to be slain– The Nephites must use all of their power and means to deliver themselves from their enemies– Moroni threatens to fight against the government unless help is supplied to his armies. About 62 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 61",
                "back": "Pahoran tells Moroni of the insurrection and rebellion against the government– The king– men take Zarahemla and are in league with the Lamanites– Pahoran asks for military aid against the rebels. About 62 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 62",
                "back": "Moroni marches to the aid of Pahoran in the land of Gideon– The king– men who refuse to defend their country are put to death– Pahoran and Moroni retake Nephihah– Many Lamanites join the people of Ammon– Teancum slays Ammoron and is in turn slain– The Lamanites are driven from the land, and peace is established– Helaman returns to the ministry and builds up the Church. About 62– 57 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Alma 63",
                "back": "Shiblon and later Helaman take possession of the sacred records– Many Nephites travel to the land northward– Hagoth builds ships, which sail forth in the west sea– Moronihah defeats the Lamanites in battle. Between 56 and 53 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Helaman": {
            "name": "Helaman",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Helaman 1",
                "back": "Pahoran the second becomes chief judge and is murdered by Kishkumen– Pacumeni fills the judgment– seat– Coriantumr leads the Lamanite armies, takes Zarahemla, and slays Pacumeni– Moronihah defeats the Lamanites and retakes Zarahemla, and Coriantumr is slain. Between 52 and 51 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 2",
                "back": "Helaman the second becomes chief judge– Gadianton leads the band of Kishkumen– Helaman’s servant slays Kishkumen, and the Gadianton band flees into the wilderness. 50 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 3",
                "back": "Many Nephites migrate to the land northward– They build houses of cement and keep many records– Tens of thousands are converted and baptized– The word of God leads men to salvation– Nephi the son of Helaman fills the judgment seat. Between 49 and 39 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 4",
                "back": "Nephite dissenters and the Lamanites join forces and take the land of Zarahemla– The Nephites’ defeats come because of their wickedness– The Church dwindles and the people become weak like the Lamanites. Between 38 and 30 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 5",
                "back": "Nephi and Lehi devote themselves to preaching– Their names invite them to pattern their lives after their forebears– Christ redeems those who repent– Nephi and Lehi make many converts and are imprisoned, and fire encircles them– A cloud of darkness overshadows three hundred people– The earth shakes and a voice commands men to repent– Nephi and Lehi converse with angels, and the multitude are encircled by fire. About 30 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 6",
                "back": "The righteous Lamanites preach to the wicked Nephites– Both peoples prosper during an era of peace and plenty– Lucifer, the author of sin, guides the Gadianton robbers in their murders and wickedness– They take over the Nephite government. Between 29 and 24 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 7",
                "back": "Nephi is rejected in the north and returns to Zarahemla– He prays upon his garden tower and then calls upon the people to repent or perish. Between 23 and 20 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 8",
                "back": "Corrupt judges seek to incite the people against Nephi– Abraham, Moses, Zenos, Zenock, Ezias, Isaiah, Jeremiah, Lehi, and Nephi all testified of Christ– By inspiration Nephi announces the murder of the chief judge. Between 23 and 20 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 9",
                "back": "Messengers find the chief judge dead at the judgment seat– They are imprisoned and later released– By inspiration Nephi identifies Seantum as the murderer– Nephi is accepted by some as a prophet. Between 23 and 20 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 10",
                "back": "The Lord gives Nephi the sealing power– He is empowered to bind and loose on earth and in heaven– He commands the people to repent or perish– The Spirit carries him from congregation to congregation. Between 23 and 20 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 11",
                "back": "Nephi persuades the Lord to replace their war with a famine– Many people perish– They repent, and Nephi importunes the Lord for rain– Nephi and Lehi receive many revelations– The Gadianton robbers entrench themselves in the land. Between 20 and 7 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 12",
                "back": "Men are unstable and foolish and quick to do evil– The Lord chastens his people– The nothingness of men compared with the power of God– In the day of judgment men shall gain everlasting life or everlasting damnation. About 7 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 13",
                "back": "Samuel the Lamanite prophesies the destruction of the Nephites unless they repent– They and their riches are cursed– They reject and stone the prophets, are encircled about by demons, and seek for happiness in doing iniquity. About 6 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 14",
                "back": "Samuel predicts light during the night and a new star at Christ’s birth– Christ redeems men from temporal and spiritual death– The signs of his death include three days of darkness, the rending of the rocks, and great upheavals of nature. About 6 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 15",
                "back": "The Lord chastened the Nephites because he loved them– Converted Lamanites are firm and steadfast in the faith– The Lord will be merciful unto the Lamanites in the latter days. About 6 B.C."
              },
              {
                "front": "Helaman 16",
                "back": "The Nephites who believe Samuel are baptized by Nephi– Samuel cannot be slain with their arrows and stones– Some harden their hearts, and others see angels– The unbelievers say it is not reasonable to believe in Christ and his coming in Jerusalem. Between 5 and 1 B.C."
              }
            ]
          },
          "3 Nephi": {
            "name": "3 Nephi",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 1",
                "back": "Nephi, son of Helaman, departs out of the land, and his son Nephi keeps the records– Though signs and wonders abound, the wicked plan to slay the righteous– The night of Christ’s birth arrives– The sign is given and a new star arises– Lyings and deceivings increase, and the Gadianton robbers slaughter many. Between A.D. 1 and 4"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 2",
                "back": "Wickedness and abominations increase among the people– The Nephites and Lamanites unite to defend themselves against the Gadianton robbers– Converted Lamanites become white and are called Nephites. Between A.D. 5 and 15"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 3",
                "back": "Giddianhi, the Gadianton leader, demands that Lachoneus and the Nephites surrender themselves and their lands– Lachoneus appoints Gidgiddoni as chief captain of the armies– The Nephites assemble in Zarahemla and Bountiful to defend themselves. Between A.D. 16 and 17"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 4",
                "back": "The Nephite armies defeat the Gadianton robbers– Giddianhi is slain, and his successor, Zemnarihah, is hanged– The Nephites praise the Lord for their victories. Between A.D. 18 and 22"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 5",
                "back": "The Nephites repent and forsake their sins– Mormon writes the history of his people and declares the everlasting word to them– Israel shall be gathered in from her long dispersion. Between A.D. 21 and 26"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 6",
                "back": "The Nephites prosper– Pride, wealth, and class distinctions arise– The Church is rent with dissensions– Satan leads the people in open rebellion– Many prophets cry repentance and are slain– Their murderers conspire to take over the government. Between A.D. 26 and 30"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 7",
                "back": "The chief judge is murdered, the government is overthrown, and the people divide into tribes– Jacob, an antichrist, becomes king of a league of tribes– Nephi preaches repentance and faith in Christ– Angels minister to him daily, and he raises his brother from the dead– Many repent and are baptized. Between A.D. 30 and 33"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 8",
                "back": "Tempests, earthquakes, fires, whirlwinds, and physical upheavals attest the crucifixion of Christ– Many people are destroyed– Darkness covers the land for three days– Those who remain bemoan their fate. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 9",
                "back": "In the darkness the voice of Christ proclaims the destruction of many people and cities for their wickedness– He also proclaims his divinity, announces that the law of Moses is fulfilled, and invites men to come unto him and be saved. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 10",
                "back": "There is silence in the land for many hours– The voice of Christ promises to gather his people as a hen gathereth her chickens– The more righteous part of the people had been preserved. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 11",
                "back": "The Father testifies of his Beloved Son– Christ appears and proclaims his atonement– The people feel the wound marks in his hands and feet and side– They cry Hosanna– He sets forth the mode and manner of baptism– The spirit of contention is of the devil– Christ’s doctrine is that men should believe and be baptized and receive the Holy Ghost. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 12",
                "back": "Jesus calls and commissions the Twelve– He delivers to the Nephites a discourse similar to the Sermon on the Mount– He speaks the Beatitudes– His teachings transcend and take precedence over the law of Moses– Men are commanded to be perfect even as he and his Father are perfect– Compare Matthew 5. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 13",
                "back": "Jesus teaches the Nephites the Lord’s Prayer– They are to lay up treasures in heaven– The Twelve in their ministry are commanded to take no thought for temporal things– Compare Matthew 6. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 14",
                "back": "Jesus commands: Judge not; ask of God; beware of false prophets– He promises salvation to those who do the will of the Father– Compare Matthew 7. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 15",
                "back": "Jesus announces that the law of Moses is fulfilled in him– The Nephites are the other sheep of whom he spake in Jerusalem– Because of iniquity the Lord’s people in Jerusalem do not know of the scattered sheep of Israel. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 16",
                "back": "Jesus will visit others of the lost sheep of Israel– In the latter days the gospel will go to the Gentiles and then to the house of Israel– The Lord’s people shall see eye to eye when he brings again Zion. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 17",
                "back": "Jesus directs the people to ponder his words and pray for understanding– He heals their sick– He prays for the people, using language that cannot be written– Angels minister to and fire encircles their little ones. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 18",
                "back": "Jesus institutes the sacrament among the Nephites– They are commanded to pray always in his name– Those who eat his flesh and drink his blood unworthily are damned– The disciples are given power to confer the Holy Ghost. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 19",
                "back": "The Twelve Disciples minister unto the people and pray for the Holy Ghost– They are baptized and receive the Holy Ghost and the ministering of angels– Jesus prays using words that cannot be written– He attests to the exceedingly great faith of these Nephites. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 20",
                "back": "Jesus provides bread and wine miraculously and again administers the sacrament unto them– The remnant of Jacob shall come to the knowledge of the Lord their God and shall inherit the Americas– Jesus is the prophet like unto Moses, and the Nephites are children of the prophets– Others of the Lord’s people shall be gathered to Jerusalem. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 21",
                "back": "Israel shall be gathered when the Book of Mormon comes forth– The Gentiles shall be established as a free people in America– They shall be saved if they believe and obey; otherwise they shall be cut off and destroyed– Israel shall build the New Jerusalem, and the lost tribes shall return. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 22",
                "back": "In the last days, Zion and her stakes shall be established, and Israel shall be gathered in mercy and tenderness– They shall triumph– Compare Isaiah 54. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 23",
                "back": "Jesus approves the words of Isaiah– He commands the people to search the prophets– The words of Samuel the Lamanite concerning the resurrection are added to their records. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 24",
                "back": "The Lord’s messenger shall prepare the way for the Second Coming– Christ shall sit in judgment– Israel is commanded to pay tithes and offerings– A book of remembrance is kept– Compare Malachi 3. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 25",
                "back": "At the Second Coming the proud and wicked shall be burned as stubble– Elijah shall return before that great and dreadful day– Compare Malachi 4. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 26",
                "back": "Jesus expounds all things from the beginning to the end– Babes and children utter marvelous things which cannot be written– Those in the Church of Christ have all things in common among them. [A.D. 34]"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 27",
                "back": "Jesus commands them to call the Church in his name– His mission and atoning sacrifice constitute his gospel– Men are commanded to repent and be baptized that they may be sanctified by the Holy Ghost– They are to be even as Jesus is. Between A.D. 34 and 35"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 28",
                "back": "Nine of the Twelve desire and are promised an inheritance in Christ’s kingdom when they die– The Three Nephites desire and are given power over death so as to remain on the earth until Jesus comes again– They are translated and see things not lawful to utter, and they are now ministering among men. Between A.D. 34 and 35"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 29",
                "back": "The coming forth of the Book of Mormon is a sign that the Lord has commenced to gather Israel and fulfill his covenants– Those who reject his latter– day revelations and gifts shall be cursed. Between A.D. 34 and 35"
              },
              {
                "front": "3 Nephi 30",
                "back": "The latter– day Gentiles are commanded to repent and come unto Christ and be numbered with the house of Israel. Between A.D. 34 and 35"
              }
            ]
          },
          "4 Nephi": {
            "name": "4 Nephi",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "4 Nephi 1",
                "back": "The Nephites and the Lamanites are all converted to the Church of Christ– They have all things in common, work miracles, and prosper in the land– After two centuries divisions, evils, false churches, and persecutions arise– After three hundred years both the Nephites and the Lamanites are wicked– Ammaron hides up the sacred records. Between A.D. 36 and 321"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Mormon": {
            "name": "Mormon",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Mormon 1",
                "back": "Ammaron instructs Mormon concerning the sacred records– War commences between the Nephites and the Lamanites– The Three Nephites are taken away– Wickedness, unbelief, sorceries, and witchcraft prevail. About A.D. 322– 326"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 2",
                "back": "Mormon leads the Nephite armies– Blood and carnage sweep the land– The Nephites lament and mourn with the sorrowing of the damned– Their day of grace is passed– Mormon obtains the plates of Nephi– Wars continue. Between A.D. 327 and 350"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 3",
                "back": "Mormon cries repentance unto the Nephites– They gain a great victory and glory in their own strength– Mormon refuses to lead them, and his prayers for them are without faith– The Book of Mormon invites the twelve tribes of Israel to believe the gospel. Between A.D. 350 and 362"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 4",
                "back": "War and carnage continue– The wicked punish the wicked– Greater wickedness prevails than ever before in all Israel– Women and children are sacrificed to idols– The Lamanites begin to sweep the Nephites before them. Between A.D. 363 and 375"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 5",
                "back": "Mormon again leads the Nephite armies in battles of blood and carnage– The Book of Mormon shall come forth to convince all Israel that Jesus is the Christ– The Lamanites shall be a dark, filthy, and loathsome people– They shall receive the gospel from the Gentiles in the latter days. Between A.D. 375 and 384"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 6",
                "back": "The Nephites gather to the land of Cumorah for the final battles– Mormon hides the sacred records in the hill Cumorah– The Lamanites are victorious, and the Nephite nation is destroyed– Hundreds of thousands are slain with the sword. [A.D. 385]"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 7",
                "back": "Mormon invites the Lamanites of the latter days to believe in Christ, accept his gospel, and be saved– All who believe the Bible will also believe the Book of Mormon. About A.D. 385"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 8",
                "back": "The Lamanites seek out and destroy the Nephites– The Book of Mormon shall come forth by the power of God– Woes pronounced upon those who breathe out wrath and strife against the work of the Lord– The Nephite record shall come forth in a day of wickedness, degeneracy, and apostasy. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Mormon 9",
                "back": "Moroni calls upon those who do not believe in Christ to repent– He proclaims a God of miracles, who gives revelations and pours out gifts and signs upon the faithful– Miracles cease because of unbelief– Signs follow those who believe– Men are exhorted to be wise and keep the commandments. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              }
            ]
          },
          "Ether": {
            "name": "Ether",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Ether 1",
                "back": "Moroni abridges the writings of Ether– Ether’s genealogy set forth– The language of the Jaredites is not confounded at the Tower of Babel– The Lord promises to lead them to a choice land and make them a great nation."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 2",
                "back": "The Jaredites prepare for their journey to a promised land– It is a choice land whereon men must serve Christ or be swept off– The Lord talks to the brother of Jared for three hours– They build barges– The Lord asks the brother of Jared to propose how the barges shall be lighted."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 3",
                "back": "The brother of Jared sees the finger of the Lord as he touches the sixteen stones– Christ shows his spirit body to the brother of Jared– Those who have a perfect knowledge cannot be kept from within the veil– Interpreters are provided to bring the Jaredite record to light."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 4",
                "back": "Moroni is commanded to seal up the writings of the brother of Jared– They shall not be revealed until men have faith even as the brother of Jared– Christ commands men to believe his words and those of his disciples– Men are commanded to repent and believe the gospel and be saved."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 5",
                "back": "Three witnesses and the work itself shall stand as a testimony of the truthfulness of the Book of Mormon."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 6",
                "back": "The Jaredite barges are driven by the winds to the promised land– The people praise the Lord for his goodness– Orihah is appointed king over them– Jared and his brother pass away in death."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 7",
                "back": "Orihah reigns in righteousness– Amid usurpation and strife the rival kingdoms of Shule and Cohor are set up– Prophets condemn the wickedness and idolatry of the people, who then repent."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 8",
                "back": "There is strife and contention over the kingdom– Akish forms an oath– bound secret combination to slay the king– Secret combinations are of the devil and result in the destruction of nations– Modern Gentiles are warned against the secret combination which shall seek to overthrow the freedom of all lands, nations, and countries."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 9",
                "back": "The kingdom passes from one to another by descent and intrigue and murder– Emer saw the Son of Righteousness– Many prophets cry repentance– A famine and poisonous serpents plague the people."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 10",
                "back": "One king succeeds another– Some of the kings are righteous; others are wicked– When righteousness prevails, the people are blessed and prospered by the Lord."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 11",
                "back": "Wars, dissensions, and wickedness dominate Jaredite life– Their prophets predict the utter destruction of the Jaredites unless they repent– The people reject the words of the prophets."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 12",
                "back": "The prophet Ether exhorts the people to believe in God– Moroni recounts the wonders and marvels done by faith– Faith enabled the brother of Jared to see Christ– The Lord gives men weaknesses that they may be humble– The brother of Jared moved Mount Zerin by faith– Faith, hope, and charity are essential to salvation– Moroni saw Jesus face to face."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 13",
                "back": "Ether speaks of a New Jerusalem to be built in America by the seed of Joseph– He prophesies, is cast out, writes the Jaredite history, and foretells the destruction of the Jaredites– War rages over all the land."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 14",
                "back": "The iniquity of the people brings a curse upon the land– Coriantumr engages in warfare against Gilead, then Lib, and then Shiz– Blood and carnage cover the land."
              },
              {
                "front": "Ether 15",
                "back": "Millions of the Jaredites are slain in battle– Shiz and Coriantumr assemble all the people to mortal combat– The Spirit of the Lord ceases to strive with them– The Jaredite nation is utterly destroyed– Only Coriantumr remains."
              }
            ]
          },
          "Moroni": {
            "name": "Moroni",
            "cards": [
              {
                "front": "Moroni 1",
                "back": "Moroni writes for the benefit of the Lamanites– The Nephites who will not deny Christ are put to death. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 2",
                "back": "Jesus gave the Nephite apostles power to confer the gift of the Holy Ghost. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 3",
                "back": "Elders ordain priests and teachers by the laying on of hands. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 4",
                "back": "How the elders and priests administer the sacramental bread. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 5",
                "back": "The mode of administering the sacramental wine is set forth. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 6",
                "back": "Repentant persons are baptized and fellowshipped– Church members who repent are forgiven– Meetings are conducted by the power of the Holy Ghost. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 7",
                "back": "An invitation to enter into the rest of the Lord– Pray with real intent– The Spirit of Christ enables men to know good from evil– Satan persuades men to deny Christ and do evil– The prophets manifest the coming of Christ– By faith miracles are wrought and angels minister– Men should hope for eternal life and cleave unto charity. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 8",
                "back": "Infant baptism is an evil abomination– Little children are alive in Christ because of the atonement– Faith, repentance, meekness and lowliness of heart, receiving the Holy Ghost, and enduring to the end lead to salvation. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 9",
                "back": "Both the Nephites and the Lamanites are depraved and degenerate– They torture and murder each other– Mormon prays that grace and goodness may rest upon Moroni forever. Between A.D. 400 and 421"
              },
              {
                "front": "Moroni 10",
                "back": "A testimony of the Book of Mormon comes by the power of the Holy Ghost– The gifts of the Spirit are dispensed to the faithful– Spiritual gifts always accompany faith– Moroni’s words speak from the dust– Come unto Christ, be perfected in him, and sanctify your souls. About A.D. 421"
              }
            ]
          }
        }
      }
    }
  }